[('This', 'O'), ('opens', 'O'), ('one', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('Seven', 'O'), ('Doors', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('Death', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('allowing', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('dead', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('cross', 'O'), ('into', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('world', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('living', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('Joe', 'PERSON'), ("'s", 'O'), ('wife', 'O'), ('Mary-Anne', 'PERSON'), ('and', 'O'), ('their', 'O'), ('daughter', 'O'), ('Jill', 'PERSON'), ('arrive', 'O'), ('at', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('hospital', 'O'), ('morgue', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('claim', 'O'), ('Joe', 'PERSON'), ("'s", 'O'), ('corpse', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('Liza', 'PERSON'), ('meets', 'O'), ('with', 'O'), ('Dr.', 'O'), ('John', 'PERSON'), ('McCabe', 'PERSON'), (',', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('receives', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('phone', 'O'), ('call', 'O'), ('informing', 'O'), ('her', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('Mary-Anne', 'PERSON'), ("'s", 'O'), ('death', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('The', 'O'), ('shop', 'O'), ('owner', 'O'), ('says', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('book', 'O'), ('has', 'O'), ('been', 'O'), ('there', 'O'), ('for', 'O'), ('years', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('prompting', 'O'), ('Liza', 'PERSON'), ('to', 'O'), ('remark', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('John', 'PERSON'), ('that', 'O'), ('perhaps', 'O'), ('it', 'O'), ('is', 'O'), ('all', 'O'), ('in', 'O'), ('her', 'O'), ('head', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('At', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('hotel', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('worker', 'O'), ('named', 'O'), ('Arthur', 'PERSON'), ('attempts', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('repair', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('same', 'O'), ('leak', 'O'), ('as', 'O'), ('Joe', 'PERSON'), (',', 'O'), ('but', 'O'), ('is', 'O'), ('killed', 'O'), ('off-screen', 'O'), ('by', 'O'), ('ghouls', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('Spiders', 'O'), ('ravage', 'O'), ('his', 'O'), ('face', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('kill', 'O'), ('him', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('Joe', 'PERSON'), ('pushes', 'O'), ('her', 'O'), ('head', 'O'), ('into', 'O'), ('an', 'O'), ('exposed', 'O'), ('nail', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('killing', 'O'), ('her', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('destroying', 'O'), ('one', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('her', 'O'), ('eyes', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('Liza', 'PERSON'), ('is', 'O'), ('attacked', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('but', 'O'), ('John', 'PERSON'), ('gets', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('gun', 'O'), ('out', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('his', 'O'), ('desk', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('shoots', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('shambling', 'O'), ('corpses', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('Only', 'O'), ('Harris', 'PERSON'), ('and', 'O'), ('Jill', 'PERSON'), ('are', 'O'), ('found', 'O'), ('still', 'O'), ('alive', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('but', 'O'), ('Harris', 'PERSON'), ('is', 'O'), ('killed', 'O'), ('by', 'O'), ('flying', 'O'), ('shards', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('glass', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('John', 'PERSON'), ('is', 'O'), ('forced', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('kill', 'O'), ('Jill', 'PERSON'), ('.', 'O')]
[('Besides', 'O'), ('changing', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('name', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('film', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('film', 'O'), ('was', 'O'), ('heavily', 'O'), ('edited', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('tone', 'O'), ('down', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('film', 'O'), ("'s", 'O'), ('graphic', 'O'), ('murder', 'O'), ('sequences', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('with', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('new', 'O'), ('musical', 'O'), ('score', 'O'), ('by', 'O'), ('Walter', 'PERSON'), ('E.', 'PERSON'), ('Sear', 'PERSON'), ('.', 'O')]
[('Alan', 'PERSON'), ("'s", 'O'), ('exploration', 'O'), ('in', 'O'), ('Haiti', 'LOCATION'), ('to', 'O'), ('find', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('drug', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('assisted', 'O'), ('by', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('doctor', 'O'), ('Marielle', 'LOCATION'), ('(', 'O'), ('Cathy', 'PERSON'), ('Tyson', 'PERSON'), (')', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('locates', 'O'), ('Christophe', 'PERSON'), ('who', 'O'), ('is', 'O'), ('alive', 'O'), ('again', 'O'), ('after', 'O'), ('having', 'O'), ('been', 'O'), ('buried', 'O'), ('for', 'O'), ('dead', 'O'), ('seven', 'O'), ('years', 'O'), ('before', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('Alan', 'PERSON'), ('pays', 'O'), ('Mozart', 'PERSON'), ('for', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('sample', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('drug', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('but', 'O'), ('Mozart', 'PERSON'), ('sells', 'O'), ('him', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('fake', 'O'), ('substitute', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('rat', 'O'), ('poison', 'O'), ('instead', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('After', 'O'), ('having', 'O'), ('his', 'O'), ('scrotum', 'O'), ('nailed', 'O'), ('into', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('chair', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('Alan', 'PERSON'), ('is', 'O'), ('dumped', 'O'), ('on', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('street', 'O'), ('with', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('message', 'O'), ('clear', 'O'), ('that', 'O'), ('he', 'O'), ('had', 'O'), ('best', 'O'), ('leave', 'O'), ('Haiti', 'LOCATION'), ('before', 'O'), ('he', 'O'), ('is', 'O'), ('killed', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('The', 'O'), ("''Tonton", 'O'), ('Macoutes', 'O'), ("''", 'O'), ('enter', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('take', 'O'), ('photos', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('frame', 'O'), ('Alan', 'PERSON'), ('for', 'O'), ('murder', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('Brought', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('Peytraud', 'LOCATION'), (',', 'O'), ('Peytraud', 'PERSON'), ('tells', 'O'), ('Alan', 'PERSON'), ('to', 'O'), ('leave', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('country', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('never', 'O'), ('return', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('lest', 'O'), ('he', 'O'), ('be', 'O'), ('convicted', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('framed', 'O'), ('murder', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('executed', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('then', 'O'), ('his', 'O'), ('soul', 'O'), ('stolen', 'O'), ('by', 'O'), ('Peytraud', 'PERSON'), ('.', 'O')]
[('At', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('celebration', 'O'), ('dinner', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('wife', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('Alan', 'PERSON'), ("'s", 'O'), ('employer', 'O'), ('is', 'O'), ('possessed', 'O'), ('by', 'O'), ('Peytraud', 'PERSON'), (',', 'O'), ('who', 'O'), ('warns', 'O'), ('Alan', 'PERSON'), ('of', 'O'), ('his', 'O'), ('own', 'O'), ('imminent', 'O'), ('death', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('Thereafter', 'O'), ('Alan', 'PERSON'), ('returns', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('Haiti', 'LOCATION'), (',', 'O'), ('where', 'O'), ('his', 'O'), ('only', 'O'), ('ally', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ("''houngan", 'O'), ("''", 'O'), ('named', 'O'), ('Lucien', 'PERSON'), ('Celine', 'PERSON'), (',', 'O'), ('is', 'O'), ('killed', 'O'), ('by', 'O'), ('Peytraud', 'PERSON'), ('through', 'O'), ('dark', 'O'), ('magic', 'O'), ('causing', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('scorpion', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('materialize', 'O'), ('inside', 'O'), ('Celine', 'PERSON'), ("'s", 'O'), ('throat', 'O'), (';', 'O'), ('Mozart', 'PERSON'), ('is', 'O'), ('beheaded', 'O'), ('at', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('same', 'O'), ('time', 'O'), ('as', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('sacrifice', 'O'), ('for', 'O'), ('Peytraud', 'O'), ("'s", 'O'), ('evil', 'O'), ('power', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('Alan', 'PERSON'), ('is', 'O'), ('then', 'O'), ('sprayed', 'O'), ('with', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('zombie', 'O'), ('powder', 'O'), ('which', 'O'), ('``', 'O'), ('kills', 'O'), ("''", 'O'), ('him', 'O'), (';', 'O'), ('afterwards', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('Peytraud', 'PERSON'), ('steals', 'O'), ('Alan', 'PERSON'), ("'s", 'O'), ('body', 'O'), ('from', 'O'), ('an', 'O'), ('American', 'O'), ('medical', 'O'), ('clinic', 'O'), ('before', 'O'), ('Alan', 'PERSON'), ("'s", 'O'), ('death', 'O'), ('can', 'O'), ('be', 'O'), ('reported', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('American', 'O'), ('Embassy', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('Peytraud', 'PERSON'), ('takes', 'O'), ('Alan', 'PERSON'), ('to', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('graveyard', 'O'), ('where', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('helpless', 'O'), ('in', 'O'), ('his', 'O'), ('coffin', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('Alan', 'PERSON'), ('sees', 'O'), ('that', 'O'), ('Peytraud', 'PERSON'), ('has', 'O'), ('captured', 'O'), ('Marielle', 'LOCATION'), ('and', 'O'), ('will', 'O'), ('kill', 'O'), ('her', 'O'), ('as', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('sacrifice', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('Baron', 'PERSON'), ('Samedi', 'PERSON'), ('.', 'O')]
[('Waking', 'O'), ('up', 'O'), ('screaming', 'O'), ('in', 'O'), ('his', 'O'), ('coffin', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('few', 'O'), ('hours', 'O'), ('later', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('Alan', 'PERSON'), ('is', 'O'), ('rescued', 'O'), ('by', 'O'), ('Christophe', 'PERSON'), ('who', 'O'), ('was', 'O'), ('also', 'O'), ('turned', 'O'), ('into', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('zombie', 'O'), ('by', 'O'), ('Peytraud', 'PERSON'), ('many', 'O'), ('years', 'O'), ('earlier', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('now', 'O'), ('lives', 'O'), ('in', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('cemetery', 'O'), ('thinking', 'O'), ('that', 'O'), ('he', 'O'), ('is', 'O'), ('still', 'O'), ('dead', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('When', 'O'), ('Curien', 'PERSON'), ('has', 'O'), ('created', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('serum', 'O'), ('that', 'O'), ('he', 'O'), ('believes', 'O'), ('will', 'O'), ('bring', 'O'), ('back', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('dead', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('grant', 'O'), ('immortality', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('Curien', 'PERSON'), ('murders', 'O'), ('one', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('his', 'O'), ('students', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('injects', 'O'), ('her', 'O'), ('with', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('serum', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('One', 'O'), ('soldier', 'O'), ('panics', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('another', 'O'), ('becomes', 'O'), ('infected', 'O'), ('after', 'O'), ('his', 'O'), ('gun', 'O'), ('jams', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('When', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('others', 'O'), ('discover', 'O'), ('his', 'O'), ('injury', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('they', 'O'), ('sever', 'O'), ('his', 'O'), ('infect', 'O'), ('arm', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('but', 'O'), ('he', 'O'), ('turns', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('infects', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('team', 'O'), ('medic', 'O'), (';', 'O'), ('both', 'O'), ('are', 'O'), ('executed', 'O'), ('by', 'O'), ('Ellis', 'PERSON'), ('.', 'O')]
[('Eventually', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('every', 'O'), ('soldier', 'O'), ('escorting', 'O'), ('them', 'O'), ('is', 'O'), ('killed', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('including', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('leader', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('unit', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('Sergeant', 'O'), ('Griffin', 'PERSON'), ('.', 'O')]
[('They', 'O'), ('enter', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('confinement', 'O'), ('room', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('extract', 'O'), ('blood', 'O'), ('from', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('zombie', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('but', 'O'), ('are', 'O'), ('forced', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('kill', 'O'), ('it', 'O'), ('when', 'O'), ('it', 'O'), ('breaks', 'O'), ('free', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('Bart', 'PERSON'), ('decides', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('kill', 'O'), ('Ellis', 'PERSON'), ('anyway', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('Nightingale', 'PERSON'), ('survives', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('kills', 'O'), ('Bart', 'PERSON'), ('.', 'O')]
[('When', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('images', 'O'), ('overwhelm', 'O'), ('her', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('Mary', 'PERSON'), ('breaks', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('circle', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('falls', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('floor', 'O'), ('as', 'O'), ('if', 'O'), ('dead', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('He', 'O'), ('discovers', 'O'), ('that', 'O'), ('Mary', 'PERSON'), ('is', 'O'), ('still', 'O'), ('alive', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('uses', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('pick', 'O'), ('axe', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('free', 'O'), ('her', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('Peter', 'PERSON'), ('and', 'O'), ('Mary', 'PERSON'), ('visit', 'O'), ('Theresa', 'PERSON'), ('who', 'O'), ('warns', 'O'), ('them', 'O'), ('that', 'O'), ('according', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('ancient', 'O'), ('book', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('Enoch', 'PERSON'), (',', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('events', 'O'), ('Mary', 'PERSON'), ('witnessed', 'O'), ('in', 'O'), ('her', 'O'), ('visions', 'O'), ('presage', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('eruption', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('living', 'O'), ('dead', 'O'), ('into', 'O'), ('our', 'O'), ('world', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('The', 'O'), ('death', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('Father', 'O'), ('Thomas', 'PERSON'), ('has', 'O'), ('somehow', 'O'), ('opened', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('door', 'O'), ('through', 'O'), ('which', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('living', 'O'), ('dead', 'O'), ('can', 'O'), ('enter', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('invasion', 'O'), ('will', 'O'), ('commence', 'O'), ('on', 'O'), ('All', 'O'), ('Saints', 'O'), ('Day', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('just', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('few', 'O'), ('days', 'O'), ('away', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('Father', 'O'), ('Thomas', 'PERSON'), ('makes', 'O'), ('Rose', 'PERSON'), ("'s", 'O'), ('eyeballs', 'O'), ('bleed', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('she', 'O'), ('meets', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('ghastly', 'O'), ('fate', 'O'), ('by', 'O'), ('vomiting', 'O'), ('her', 'O'), ('entire', 'O'), ('guts', 'O'), ('out', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('Tommy', 'PERSON'), ('is', 'O'), ('killed', 'O'), ('by', 'O'), ('getting', 'O'), ('his', 'O'), ('head', 'O'), ('ripped', 'O'), ('open', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('At', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('local', 'O'), ('morgue', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('mortician', 'O'), ('is', 'O'), ('bitten', 'O'), ('on', 'O'), ('his', 'O'), ('hand', 'O'), ('by', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('cadaver', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('elderly', 'O'), ('Jane', 'PERSON'), ('Holden', 'PERSON'), ('while', 'O'), ('trying', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('steal', 'O'), ('her', 'O'), ('jewelry', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('The', 'O'), ('apparition', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('dead', 'O'), ('Emily', 'PERSON'), ('pays', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('nocturnal', 'O'), ('visit', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('her', 'O'), ('little', 'O'), ('brother', 'O'), ('John-John', 'PERSON'), ('(', 'O'), ('Luca', 'PERSON'), ('Paisner', 'PERSON'), (')', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('When', 'O'), ('it', 'O'), ("'s", 'O'), ('over', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('Gerry', 'PERSON'), ('receives', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('distressing', 'O'), ('phone', 'O'), ('call', 'O'), ('from', 'O'), ('John-John', 'PERSON'), ('Robbins', 'PERSON'), ('explaining', 'O'), ('his', 'O'), ('dead', 'O'), ('sister', 'O'), ('has', 'O'), ('returned', 'O'), ('from', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('grave', 'O'), ('during', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('night', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('killed', 'O'), ('his', 'O'), ('parents', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('Upon', 'O'), ('arriving', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('her', 'O'), ('apartment', 'O'), ('building', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('Sandra', 'PERSON'), ('is', 'O'), ('killed', 'O'), ('by', 'O'), ('Emily', 'PERSON'), (',', 'O'), ('who', 'O'), ('rips', 'O'), ('Sandra', 'PERSON'), ("'s", 'O'), ('scalp', 'O'), ('off', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('At', 'O'), ('Junie', 'PERSON'), ("'s", 'O'), ('Lounge', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('Mr.', 'O'), ('Ross', 'PERSON'), (',', 'O'), ('Mike', 'PERSON'), (',', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('barman', 'O'), ('are', 'O'), ('attacked', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('finally', 'O'), ('killed', 'O'), ('by', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('marauding', 'O'), ('ghouls', 'O'), ('as', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('state-of-emergency', 'O'), ('is', 'O'), ('declared', 'O'), ('over', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('radio', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('Sandra', 'PERSON'), ('suddenly', 'O'), ('appears', 'O'), ('as', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('zombie', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('kills', 'O'), ('Peter', 'PERSON'), ('by', 'O'), ('ripping', 'O'), ('his', 'O'), ('brains', 'O'), ('out', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('Gerry', 'PERSON'), ('impales', 'O'), ('her', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('cave', 'O'), ('wall', 'O'), ('with', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('pitchfork', 'O'), ('through', 'O'), ('her', 'O'), ('chest', 'O'), ('before', 'O'), ('she', 'O'), ('can', 'O'), ('kill', 'O'), ('Mary', 'PERSON'), ('.', 'O')]
[('The', 'O'), ('Gates', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('Hell', 'O'), ('have', 'O'), ('been', 'O'), ('closed', 'O'), ('just', 'O'), ('before', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('dead', 'O'), ('fully', 'O'), ('rise', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('Post-Video', 'O'), ('Recordings', 'O'), ('Act', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('it', 'O'), ('was', 'O'), ('submitted', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('BBFC', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('for', 'O'), ('official', 'O'), ('video', 'O'), ('release', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('received', 'O'), ('further', 'O'), ('cuts', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('vomiting', 'O'), ('scene', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('brain', 'O'), ('crushing', 'O'), ('scenes', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('When', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('zombies', 'O'), ('run', 'O'), ('out', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('alligators', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('eat', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('they', 'O'), ('begin', 'O'), ('killing', 'O'), ('people', 'O'), ('in', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('town', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('William', 'PERSON'), ('saves', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('young', 'O'), ('girl', 'O'), ('from', 'O'), ('being', 'O'), ('raped', 'O'), ('but', 'O'), ('is', 'O'), ('killed', 'O'), ('when', 'O'), ('one', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('rapists', 'O'), ('fatally', 'O'), ('stabs', 'O'), ('him', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('As', 'O'), ('he', 'O'), ('steps', 'O'), ('out', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('store', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('into', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('road', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('he', 'O'), ('is', 'O'), ('run', 'O'), ('over', 'O'), ('by', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('gang', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('reckless', 'O'), ('teenagers', 'O'), ('consisting', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('Bob', 'PERSON'), ('(', 'O'), ('Allan', 'PERSON'), ('Fisler', 'PERSON'), (')', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('Amy', 'PERSON'), ('(', 'O'), ('Tia', 'PERSON'), ('Carrere', 'PERSON'), (')', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('Jim', 'PERSON'), ('(', 'O'), ('Shawn', 'PERSON'), ('Levy', 'PERSON'), (')', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('Peter', 'PERSON'), ('(', 'O'), ('Hamish', 'PERSON'), ('McEwan', 'PERSON'), (')', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('Susie', 'PERSON'), ('(', 'O'), ('Manon', 'PERSON'), ('E.', 'PERSON'), ('Turbide', 'PERSON'), (')', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('is', 'O'), ('killed', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('Bela', 'PERSON'), ('Lugosi', 'PERSON'), ('stars', 'O'), ('as', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('antagonist', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('Murder', 'PERSON'), ('Legendre', 'PERSON'), (',', 'O'), ('with', 'O'), ('Madge', 'PERSON'), ('Bellamy', 'PERSON'), ('appearing', 'O'), ('as', 'O'), ('his', 'O'), ('victim', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('Shortly', 'O'), ('after', 'O'), ('Madeleine', 'PERSON'), ('and', 'O'), ('Neil', 'PERSON'), ("'s", 'O'), ('wedding', 'O'), ('ceremony', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('potion', 'O'), ('takes', 'O'), ('effect', 'O'), ('on', 'O'), ('Madeleine', 'PERSON'), ('and', 'O'), ('she', 'O'), ('appears', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('die', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('As', 'O'), ('Neil', 'PERSON'), ('enters', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('fortress', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('Murder', 'O'), ('senses', 'O'), ('his', 'O'), ('presence', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('silently', 'O'), ('orders', 'O'), ('Madeleine', 'PERSON'), ('to', 'O'), ('kill', 'O'), ('Neil', 'PERSON'), ('.', 'O')]
[('She', 'O'), ('approaches', 'O'), ('Neil', 'PERSON'), ('with', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('knife', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('but', 'O'), ('Bruner', 'PERSON'), ('stops', 'O'), ('her', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('Neil', 'PERSON'), ('follows', 'O'), ('Madeleine', 'PERSON'), ('to', 'O'), ('an', 'O'), ('escarpment', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('where', 'O'), ('Murder', 'O'), ('commands', 'O'), ('his', 'O'), ('zombie', 'O'), ('guardians', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('kill', 'O'), ('Neil', 'PERSON'), ('.', 'O')]
[('Charles', 'PERSON'), ('loses', 'O'), ('his', 'O'), ('balance', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('also', 'O'), ('falls', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('his', 'O'), ('death', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('Murder', 'O'), ("'s", 'O'), ('death', 'O'), ('releases', 'O'), ('Madeleine', 'PERSON'), ('from', 'O'), ('her', 'O'), ('zombie', 'O'), ('trance', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('she', 'O'), ('awakens', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('embrace', 'O'), ('Neil', 'PERSON'), ('.', 'O')]
[('By', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('time', 'O'), ('Lugosi', 'PERSON'), ('appeared', 'O'), ('in', 'O'), ("''White", 'O'), ('Zombie', 'O'), ("''", 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('he', 'O'), ('was', 'O'), ('already', 'O'), ('popular', 'O'), ('with', 'O'), ('contemporary', 'O'), ('audiences', 'O'), ('after', 'O'), ('his', 'O'), ('starring', 'O'), ('role', 'O'), ('in', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('hit', 'O'), ('1931', 'O'), ('film', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ("''Dracula", 'O'), ('(', 'O'), ('1931', 'O'), ('English-language', 'O'), ('film', 'O'), (')', 'O'), ('|Dracula', 'O'), ("''", 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('Other', 'O'), ('horror', 'O'), ('films', 'O'), ('from', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('1930s', 'O'), ('borrowed', 'O'), ('themes', 'O'), ('from', 'O'), ("''White", 'O'), ('Zombie', 'O'), ("''", 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('such', 'O'), ('as', 'O'), ('people', 'O'), ('returning', 'O'), ('from', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('dead', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('other', 'O'), ('elements', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('zombie', 'O'), ('mythology.Kay', 'O'), ('2008', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('p.', 'O'), ('5', 'O'), ('These', 'O'), ('films', 'O'), ('include', 'O'), (':', 'O'), ("''The", 'O'), ('Ghost', 'O'), ('Breakers', 'O'), ("''", 'O'), ('(', 'O'), ('1940', 'O'), (')', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ("''King", 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('Zombies', 'O'), ("''", 'O'), ('(', 'O'), ('1941', 'O'), (')', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ("''I", 'O'), ('Walked', 'O'), ('with', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('Zombie', 'O'), ("''", 'O'), ('(', 'O'), ('1943', 'O'), (')', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ("''The", 'O'), ('Plague', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('Zombies', 'O'), ("''", 'O'), ('(', 'O'), ('1966', 'O'), (')', 'O'), ('.Rhodes', 'O'), ('2001', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('p.', 'O'), ('183', 'O'), ('These', 'O'), ('films', 'O'), ('all', 'O'), ('contain', 'O'), ('elements', 'O'), ('from', 'O'), ("''White", 'O'), ('Zombie', 'O'), ("''", 'O'), ('including', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('blank-eyed', 'O'), ('stares', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('voodoo', 'O'), ('drums', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('zombies', 'O'), ('performing', 'O'), ('manual', 'O'), ('labor.Rhodes', 'O'), ('2001', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('p.', 'O'), ('184', 'O')]
[('Victor', 'PERSON'), ('Halperin', 'PERSON'), ('directed', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ("''White", 'O'), ('Zombie', 'O'), ("''", 'O'), ('sequel', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ("''Revolt", 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('Zombies', 'O'), ("''", 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('which', 'O'), ('was', 'O'), ('released', 'O'), ('in', 'O'), ('1936', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[("'", 'O'), ("''", 'O'), ("''Hood", 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('Living', 'O'), ('Dead', 'O'), ("''", 'O'), ("'", 'O'), ("''", 'O'), ('is', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('2005', 'O'), ('direct-to-video', 'O'), ('zombie', 'O'), ('movie', 'O'), ('about', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('regenerative', 'O'), ('formula', 'O'), ('bringing', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('dead', 'O'), ('back', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('life', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('Since', 'O'), ('his', 'O'), ('parents', 'O'), ('died', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('Ricky', 'PERSON'), ('has', 'O'), ('been', 'O'), ('working', 'O'), ('hard', 'O'), ('at', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('laboratory', 'O'), ('trying', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('perfect', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('regenerative', 'O'), ('formula', 'O'), ('that', 'O'), ('could', 'O'), ('heal', 'O'), ('dead', 'O'), ('cells', 'O'), ('in', 'O'), ('animals', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('Ricky', 'PERSON'), ('disapproves', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('Jermaine', 'PERSON'), ("'s", 'O'), ('friends', 'O'), ('Marco', 'PERSON'), ('(', 'O'), ('Raul', 'PERSON'), ('Martinez', 'PERSON'), (')', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('Kevin', 'PERSON'), ('(', 'O'), ('Derek', 'PERSON'), ('Taylor', 'PERSON'), ('II', 'O'), (')', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('tells', 'O'), ('his', 'O'), ('brother', 'O'), ('that', 'O'), ('they', 'O'), ('will', 'O'), ('be', 'O'), ('moving', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('safer', 'O'), ('community', 'O'), ('at', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('end', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('month', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('That', 'O'), ('night', 'O'), ('Jermaine', 'PERSON'), ('is', 'O'), ('killed', 'O'), ('in', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('drive', 'O'), ('by', 'O'), ('shooting', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('The', 'O'), ('now-undead', 'O'), ('Dr.', 'O'), ('Richards', 'PERSON'), ('attacks', 'O'), ('Ricky', 'PERSON'), (',', 'O'), ('but', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('also-undead', 'O'), ('Jermaine', 'PERSON'), ('comes', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('Ricky', 'PERSON'), ("'s", 'O'), ('rescue', 'O'), ('by', 'O'), ('killing', 'O'), ('Richards', 'PERSON'), ('.', 'O')]
[('The', 'O'), ('group', 'O'), ('includes', 'O'), ('Colonel', 'O'), ('Mazovia', 'PERSON'), (';', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('student', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('dead', 'O'), ('languages', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('Armand', 'PERSON'), ('Louque', 'PERSON'), ('(', 'O'), ('Dean', 'PERSON'), ('Jagger', 'PERSON'), (')', 'O'), (';', 'O'), ('Englishman', 'O'), ('Clifford', 'PERSON'), ('Grayson', 'PERSON'), ('(', 'O'), ('Robert', 'PERSON'), ('Noland', 'PERSON'), (')', 'O'), (';', 'O'), ('General', 'O'), ('Duval', 'PERSON'), ('(', 'O'), ('George', 'PERSON'), ('Cleveland', 'PERSON'), (')', 'O'), (';', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('his', 'O'), ('daughter', 'O'), ('Claire', 'PERSON'), ('(', 'O'), ('Dorothy', 'PERSON'), ('Stone', 'PERSON'), (')', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('The', 'O'), ('recently', 'O'), ('deceased', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('an', 'O'), ('anonymous', 'O'), ('French', 'O'), ('town', 'O'), ('suddenly', 'O'), ('return', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('life', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('calmly', 'O'), ('streaming', 'O'), ('forth', 'O'), ('from', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('cemetary', 'O'), ('in', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('silent', 'O'), ('procession', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('The', 'O'), ('film', 'O'), ('plunges', 'O'), ('into', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('nightmarish', 'O'), ('experiences', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('portly', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('depressed', 'O'), ('psychic', 'O'), ('(', 'O'), ('Deborah', 'PERSON'), ('Rose', 'PERSON'), (')', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('whose', 'O'), ('involvement', 'O'), ('in', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('grisly', 'O'), ('child-murder', 'O'), ('case', 'O'), ('leads', 'O'), ('her', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('her', 'O'), ('detective', 'O'), ('partner', 'O'), ('(', 'O'), ('Ed', 'PERSON'), ('Nelson', 'PERSON'), (')', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('an', 'O'), ('imposing', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('fortress-like', 'O'), ('mortuary', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('When', 'O'), ('Chen', 'PERSON'), ('is', 'O'), ('jailed', 'O'), ('on', 'O'), ('murder', 'O'), ('charges', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('under-fed', 'O'), ('ghouls', 'O'), ('awaken', 'O'), ('in', 'O'), ('search', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('dinner', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('trapping', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('staff', 'O'), ('inside', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('mortuary', 'O'), ('walls', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('devouring', 'O'), ('them', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('The', 'O'), ('survivors', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('including', 'O'), ('Rose', 'PERSON'), ('and', 'O'), ('Nelson', 'PERSON'), (',', 'O'), ('use', 'O'), ('every', 'O'), ('means', 'O'), ('at', 'O'), ('their', 'O'), ('disposal', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('combat', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('demons', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('which', 'O'), ('have', 'O'), ('possessed', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('bodies', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('morgue', 'O'), ('attendant', 'O'), ('Mrs.', 'O'), ('Poopinplatz', 'PERSON'), ('(', 'O'), ('Phyllis', 'PERSON'), ('Diller', 'PERSON'), (')', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('her', 'O'), ('poodle', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('mutating', 'O'), ('them', 'O'), ('into', 'O'), ('hideous', 'O'), ('monsters', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('At', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('camp', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('Mac', 'O'), ('finds', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('radio', 'O'), ('dead', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('while', 'O'), ('Tyler', 'PERSON'), ('and', 'O'), ('Rita', 'PERSON'), ('begin', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('become', 'O'), ('close', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('They', 'O'), ('are', 'O'), ('rescued', 'O'), ('by', 'O'), ('another', 'O'), ('renegade', 'O'), ('band', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('surviving', 'O'), ('loggers', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('who', 'O'), ('reveal', 'O'), ('that', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('company', 'O'), ('plans', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('kill', 'O'), ('them', 'O'), ('all', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('The', 'O'), ('militaristic', 'O'), ('nature', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('camp', 'O'), ('disturbs', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('remaining', 'O'), ('survivors', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('especially', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('sadistic', 'O'), ('game', 'O'), ('they', 'O'), ('play', 'O'), ('in', 'O'), ('which', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('selected', 'O'), ('member', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('camp', 'O'), ('must', 'O'), ('kill', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('certain', 'O'), ('number', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('zombies', 'O'), ('in', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('pen', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('The', 'O'), ('next', 'O'), ('day', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('Carter', 'PERSON'), ('is', 'O'), ('selected', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('enter', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('pen', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('but', 'O'), ('he', 'O'), ('becomes', 'O'), ('frightened', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('jams', 'O'), ('his', 'O'), ('gun', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('ending', 'O'), ('up', 'O'), ('needing', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('be', 'O'), ('rescued', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('His', 'O'), ('spirit', 'O'), ('broken', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('Carter', 'PERSON'), ('takes', 'O'), ('an', 'O'), ('axe', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('leaves', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('camp', 'O'), ('alone', 'O'), ('that', 'O'), ('night', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('Zombies', 'O'), ('wander', 'O'), ('in', 'O'), ('through', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('open', 'O'), ('gate', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('kill', 'O'), ('everyone', 'O'), ('except', 'O'), ('Mac', 'PERSON'), (',', 'O'), ('Rita', 'PERSON'), ('and', 'O'), ('Tyler', 'PERSON'), (',', 'O'), ('who', 'O'), ('wake', 'O'), ('up', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('flee', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('He', 'O'), ('picks', 'O'), ('her', 'O'), ('up', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('carries', 'O'), ('her', 'O'), ('outside', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('she', 'O'), ('bites', 'O'), ('his', 'O'), ('neck', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('Mark', 'PERSON'), ('wakes', 'O'), ('up', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('thinks', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('himself', 'O'), ('about', 'O'), ('how', 'O'), ('he', 'O'), ('does', 'O'), ("n't", 'O'), ('know', 'O'), ('how', 'O'), ('long', 'O'), ('he', 'O'), ("'s", 'O'), ('been', 'O'), ('unconscious', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('admits', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('killing', 'O'), ('his', 'O'), ('first', 'O'), ('victim', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('camper', 'O'), ('in', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('woods', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('He', 'O'), ('collapses', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('suffers', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('minor', 'O'), ('seizure', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('reports', 'O'), ('it', 'O'), ('in', 'O'), ('his', 'O'), ('digital', 'O'), ('log', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('along', 'O'), ('with', 'O'), ('how', 'O'), ('he', 'O'), ('has', 'O'), ('not', 'O'), ('eaten', 'O'), ('in', 'O'), ('six', 'O'), ('days', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('has', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('find', 'O'), ('another', 'O'), ('victim', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('His', 'O'), ('leg', 'O'), ('breaks', 'O'), ('during', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('disposal', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('victim', 'O'), ("'s", 'O'), ('body', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('he', 'O'), ('is', 'O'), ('forced', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('attach', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('metal', 'O'), ('rod', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('support', 'O'), ('his', 'O'), ('ankle', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('Sometime', 'O'), ('later', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('his', 'O'), ('family', 'O'), ('receives', 'O'), ('notice', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('his', 'O'), ('death', 'O'), ('in', 'O'), ('combat', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('Hours', 'O'), ('later', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('in', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('middle', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('night', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('Andy', 'PERSON'), ('arrives', 'O'), ('at', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('front', 'O'), ('door', 'O'), ('in', 'O'), ('full', 'O'), ('uniform', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('apparently', 'O'), ('unharmed', 'O'), (';', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('family', 'O'), ('accepts', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('notice', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('his', 'O'), ('death', 'O'), ('as', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('clerical', 'O'), ('error', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('welcomes', 'O'), ('him', 'O'), ('back', 'O'), ('with', 'O'), ('joy', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('Meanwhile', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('local', 'O'), ('police', 'O'), ('investigate', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('murder', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('local', 'O'), ('trucker', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('who', 'O'), ('was', 'O'), ('found', 'O'), ('with', 'O'), ('his', 'O'), ('throat', 'O'), ('slashed', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('his', 'O'), ('body', 'O'), ('drained', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('blood', 'O'), ('after', 'O'), ('telling', 'O'), ('diner', 'O'), ('patrons', 'O'), ('that', 'O'), ('he', 'O'), ("'d", 'O'), ('picked', 'O'), ('up', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('hitchhiking', 'O'), ('soldier', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('They', 'O'), ('later', 'O'), ('try', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('escape', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('are', 'O'), ('shot', 'O'), ('dead', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('They', 'O'), ('are', 'O'), ('buried', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('rise', 'O'), ('again', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('kill', 'O'), ('everyone', 'O'), ('in', 'O'), ('their', 'O'), ('path', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('find', 'O'), ('more', 'O'), ('formaldehyde', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('get', 'O'), ('high', 'O'), ('from', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('The', 'O'), ('group', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('tourists', 'O'), ('take', 'O'), ('refuge', 'O'), ('in', 'O'), ('an', 'O'), ('old', 'O'), ('mansion', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('one', 'O'), ('by', 'O'), ('one', 'O'), ('falling', 'O'), ('victim', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('an', 'O'), ('unknown', 'O'), ('menace', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('In', 'O'), ('New', 'LOCATION'), ('York', 'LOCATION'), ('City', 'LOCATION'), ('a', 'O'), ('hospital', 'O'), ('worker', 'O'), ('is', 'O'), ('found', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('have', 'O'), ('been', 'O'), ('devouring', 'O'), ('bodies', 'O'), ('in', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('morgue', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('In', 'O'), ('this', 'O'), ('film', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('it', 'O'), ('is', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('island', 'O'), ('native', 'O'), ('people', 'O'), ('that', 'O'), ('hunt', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('kill', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('consume', 'O'), ('humans', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('By', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('conclusion', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('in', 'O'), ('which', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('film', 'O'), ('goes', 'O'), ('back', 'O'), ('in', 'O'), ('time', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('first', 'O'), ('nights', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('documentary', 'O'), ('crew', 'O'), ('at', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('beginning', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('first', 'O'), ('diary', 'O'), ('(', 'O'), ('``', 'O'), ('The', 'O'), ('Outbreak', 'O'), ("''", 'O'), (')', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('word', 'O'), ('``', 'O'), ('survivors', 'O'), ("''", 'O'), ('becomes', 'O'), ('an', 'O'), ('ironic', 'O'), ('title', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('as', 'O'), ('all', 'O'), ('but', 'O'), ('one', 'O'), ('are', 'O'), ('killed', 'O'), ('by', 'O'), ('two', 'O'), ('uninfected', 'O'), ('psychopaths', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('After', 'O'), ('some', 'O'), ('amusing', 'O'), ('introductions', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('Matool', 'PERSON'), ('inquires', 'O'), ('as', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('identity', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('man', 'O'), ('who', 'O'), ('was', 'O'), ('just', 'O'), ('killed', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('young', 'O'), ('woman', 'O'), ('replies', 'O'), ('that', 'O'), ('it', 'O'), ('was', 'O'), ('her', 'O'), ('brother', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('much', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('Matool', 'PERSON'), ("'s", 'O'), ('joy', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('but', 'O'), ('she', 'O'), ('is', 'O'), ('incensed', 'O'), ('by', 'O'), ('his', 'O'), ('subtle', 'O'), ('advances', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('still', 'O'), ('believes', 'O'), ('that', 'O'), ('they', 'O'), ('can', 'O'), ('save', 'O'), ('her', 'O'), ('now-dead', 'O'), ('brother', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('Sepulveda', 'O'), ('is', 'O'), ('placed', 'O'), ('in', 'O'), ('an', 'O'), ('unoccupied', 'O'), ('bedroom', 'O'), ('where', 'O'), ('Mandel', 'PERSON'), ('and', 'O'), ('Vega', 'PERSON'), ('take', 'O'), ('turns', 'O'), ('watching', 'O'), ('him', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('knowing', 'O'), ('that', 'O'), ('death', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('reanimation', 'O'), ('are', 'O'), ('inevitable', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('As', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('days', 'O'), ('pass', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('Vega', 'PERSON'), ('and', 'O'), ('Sassy', 'O'), ('begin', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('relationship', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('while', 'O'), ('Sepulveda', 'PERSON'), ('continues', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('die', 'O'), ('in', 'O'), ('agony', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('while', 'O'), ('Mandel', 'PERSON'), ('resists', 'O'), ('Matool', 'PERSON'), ("'s", 'O'), ('suggestion', 'O'), ('that', 'O'), ('he', 'O'), ('be', 'O'), ('put', 'O'), ('down', 'O'), ('right', 'O'), ('away', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('Meanwhile', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('Sepulveda', 'PERSON'), ('wakes', 'O'), ('up', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('sees', 'O'), ('Sassy', 'O'), ('for', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('first', 'O'), ('time', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('as', 'O'), ('well', 'O'), ('as', 'O'), ('her', 'O'), ('conjoined', 'O'), ('twin', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('freaking', 'O'), ('out', 'O'), ('at', 'O'), ('how', 'O'), ('disgusting', 'O'), ('it', 'O'), ('is', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('causing', 'O'), ('Sassy', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('lose', 'O'), ('it', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('kill', 'O'), ('him', 'O'), ('with', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('pair', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('scissors', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('Mandel', 'PERSON'), (',', 'O'), ('who', 'O'), ('was', 'O'), ('watching', 'O'), ('Sepulveda', 'PERSON'), (',', 'O'), ('instinctively', 'O'), ('shoots', 'O'), ('Sassy', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('killing', 'O'), ('her', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('Nathan', 'PERSON'), ('goes', 'O'), ('out', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('shed', 'O'), ('for', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('tryst', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('but', 'O'), ('is', 'O'), ('killed', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('devoured', 'O'), ('by', 'O'), ('his', 'O'), ('zombie', 'O'), ('companion', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('Matool', 'PERSON'), ('smashes', 'O'), ('Sassy', 'O'), ("'s", 'O'), ('head', 'O'), ('with', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('cinder', 'O'), ('block', 'O'), ('over', 'O'), ('Vega', 'PERSON'), ("'s", 'O'), ('objections', 'O'), ('who', 'O'), ('is', 'O'), ('then', 'O'), ('attacked', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('killed', 'O'), ('by', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('reanimated', 'O'), ('Sepulveda', 'PERSON'), ('.', 'O')]
[('As', 'O'), ('more', 'O'), ('zombies', 'O'), ('begin', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('gather', 'O'), ('at', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('house', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('Matool', 'PERSON'), ('demands', 'O'), ('that', 'O'), ('Mandel', 'PERSON'), ('go', 'O'), ('back', 'O'), ('into', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('house', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('get', 'O'), ('his', 'O'), ('MP5', 'O'), ('submachine', 'O'), ('gun', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('but', 'O'), ('he', 'O'), ('ca', 'O'), ("n't", 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('as', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('boy', 'O'), ('has', 'O'), ('locked', 'O'), ('them', 'O'), ('out', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('Mandel', 'PERSON'), ('then', 'O'), ('kills', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('Sepulveda', 'LOCATION'), ('zombie', 'O'), ('with', 'O'), ('his', 'O'), ('knife', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('At', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('beginning', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('movie', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('Garberina', 'PERSON'), ("'s", 'O'), ('character', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('while', 'O'), ('working', 'O'), ('as', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('video', 'O'), ('store', 'O'), ('clerk', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('is', 'O'), ('causally', 'O'), ('reading', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('newspaper', 'O'), ('article', 'O'), ('showing', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('still', 'O'), ('shot', 'O'), ('from', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('end', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ("''The", 'O'), ('Stink', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('Flesh', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ("''", 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('article', 'O'), ('explaining', 'O'), ('that', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('soldier', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('carpenter', 'O'), ('have', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('story', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('tell', 'O'), ('about', 'O'), ('their', 'O'), ('experiences', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('debauchery', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('On', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('routine', 'O'), ('flight', 'O'), ('from', 'O'), ('Los', 'LOCATION'), ('Angeles', 'LOCATION'), ('to', 'O'), ('Paris', 'LOCATION'), (',', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('wikt', 'O'), (':', 'O'), ('renegade|renegade', 'O'), ('group', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('scientists', 'O'), ('has', 'O'), ('smuggled', 'O'), ('aboard', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('secret', 'O'), ('container', 'O'), ('holding', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('fellow', 'O'), ('scientist', 'O'), ('infected', 'O'), ('with', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('deadly', 'O'), ('genetically', 'O'), ('engineered', 'O'), ('virus', 'O'), ('which', 'O'), ('reanimates', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('dead', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('Two', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('scientists', 'O'), ('go', 'O'), ('below', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('ascertain', 'O'), ('if', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('container', 'O'), ('has', 'O'), ('been', 'O'), ('damaged', 'O'), ('by', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('turbulence', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('are', 'O'), ('also', 'O'), ('killed', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('starting', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('zombie', 'O'), ('outbreak', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('After', 'O'), ('managing', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('get', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('MP5K', 'O'), ('machine', 'O'), ('gun', 'O'), ('from', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('dead', 'O'), ('guard', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('Burrows', 'PERSON'), (',', 'O'), ('Frank', 'PERSON'), ('and', 'O'), ('Billy', 'PERSON'), ('make', 'O'), ('their', 'O'), ('way', 'O'), ('from', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('tail', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('plane', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('cockpit', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('while', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('couple', 'O'), ('stay', 'O'), ('behind', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('Billy', 'PERSON'), ('is', 'O'), ('bitten', 'O'), ('but', 'O'), ('manages', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('kill', 'O'), ('some', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('undead', 'O'), ('passengers', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('while', 'O'), ('Anna', 'PERSON'), ('comes', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('help', 'O'), ('Billy', 'PERSON'), ('she', 'O'), ('gets', 'O'), ('bitten', 'O'), ('but', 'O'), ('kills', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('Undead', 'O'), ('by', 'O'), ('thrusting', 'O'), ('an', 'O'), ('umbrella', 'O'), ('into', 'O'), ('its', 'O'), ('mouth', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('Frank', 'PERSON'), ('and', 'O'), ('Burrows', 'O'), ('try', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('control', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('plane', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('but', 'O'), ('hit', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('mountain', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('crash', 'O'), ('land', 'O'), ('near', 'O'), ('Las', 'LOCATION'), ('Vegas', 'LOCATION'), (',', 'O'), ('Nevada', 'LOCATION'), ('.', 'O')]
[('The', 'O'), ('B', 'O'), ('movie', 'O'), ('is', 'O'), ('about', 'O'), ('an', 'O'), ('LAPD', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('police', 'O'), ('officer', 'O'), ('who', 'O'), ('is', 'O'), ('murdered', 'O'), ('while', 'O'), ('attempting', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('arrest', 'O'), ('zombies', 'O'), ('who', 'O'), ('have', 'O'), ('been', 'O'), ('reanimated', 'O'), ('by', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('head', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('Dante', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Laboratories', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('in', 'O'), ('order', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('carry', 'O'), ('out', 'O'), ('violent', 'O'), ('armed', 'O'), ('robberies', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('decides', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('get', 'O'), ('revenge', 'O'), ('with', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('help', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('his', 'O'), ('former', 'O'), ('partner', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('Meanwhile', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('coroner', 'O'), ('friend', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('Roger', 'PERSON'), ("'s", 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('Rebecca', 'PERSON'), ('(', 'O'), ('Clare', 'PERSON'), ('Kirkconnell', 'PERSON'), (')', 'O'), ('informs', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('detectives', 'O'), ('that', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('two', 'O'), ('bodies', 'O'), ('they', 'O'), ('had', 'O'), ('brought', 'O'), ('in', 'O'), ('had', 'O'), ('previously', 'O'), ('been', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('morgue', 'O'), (':', 'O'), ('not', 'O'), ('only', 'O'), ('do', 'O'), ('they', 'O'), ('have', 'O'), ('autopsy', 'O'), ('scars', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('but', 'O'), ('she', 'O'), ('herself', 'O'), ('clearly', 'O'), ('remembers', 'O'), ('performing', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('autopsy', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('has', 'O'), ('pictures', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('prove', 'O'), ('it', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('suggesting', 'O'), ('they', 'O'), ('simply', 'O'), ('got', 'O'), ('up', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('left', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('morgue', 'O'), ('at', 'O'), ('their', 'O'), ('own', 'O'), ('volition', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('When', 'O'), ('Doug', 'PERSON'), ('wanders', 'O'), ('off', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('investigate', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('suspicious', 'O'), ('room', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('he', 'O'), ('encounters', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('reanimated', 'O'), ('corpse', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('biker', 'O'), ('on', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('strange', 'O'), ('machine', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('in', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('fray', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('Roger', 'PERSON'), ('is', 'O'), ('knocked', 'O'), ('into', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('decompression', 'O'), ('room', 'O'), ('used', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('humanely', 'O'), ('kill', 'O'), ('failed', 'O'), ('test', 'O'), ('animals', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('is', 'O'), ('asphyxiated', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('death', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('Encountering', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('machine', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('realizing', 'O'), ('it', 'O'), ('is', 'O'), ('capable', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('bringing', 'O'), ('people', 'O'), ('back', 'O'), ('from', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('dead', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('Rebecca', 'PERSON'), ('and', 'O'), ('Doug', 'PERSON'), ('successfully', 'O'), ('bring', 'O'), ('Roger', 'PERSON'), ('back', 'O'), ('from', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('dead', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('He', 'O'), ('says', 'O'), ('he', 'O'), ('feels', 'O'), ('fine', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('yet', 'O'), ('he', 'O'), ('has', 'O'), ('no', 'O'), ('heart', 'O'), ('beat', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('his', 'O'), ('skin', 'O'), ('is', 'O'), ('cold', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('touch', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('Rebecca', 'PERSON'), ('surmises', 'O'), ('he', 'O'), ('has', 'O'), ('about', 'O'), ('twelve', 'O'), ('hours', 'O'), ('before', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('reanimation', 'O'), ('process', 'O'), ('ends', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('he', 'O'), ('dissolves', 'O'), ('into', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('puddle', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('mush', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('Roger', 'PERSON'), ('decides', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('take', 'O'), ('this', 'O'), ('time', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('find', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('exact', 'O'), ('his', 'O'), ('vengeance', 'O'), ('on', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('person', 'O'), ('who', 'O'), ('killed', 'O'), ('him', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('Randi', 'PERSON'), ('says', 'O'), ('that', 'O'), ('she', 'O'), ('is', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('daughter', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('rich', 'O'), ('industrialist', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('owner', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('company', 'O'), ('she', 'O'), ('works', 'O'), ('for', 'O'), ('until', 'O'), ('his', 'O'), ('death', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('Arthur', 'PERSON'), ('P.', 'PERSON'), ('Laudermilk', 'PERSON'), ('(', 'O'), ('Vincent', 'O'), ('Price', 'O'), (')', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('The', 'O'), ('two', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('them', 'O'), ('pay', 'O'), ('another', 'O'), ('visit', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('Rebecca', 'PERSON'), (',', 'O'), ('who', 'O'), ('says', 'O'), ('that', 'O'), ('she', 'O'), ('might', 'O'), ('have', 'O'), ('found', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('way', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('keep', 'O'), ('Roger', 'PERSON'), ('in', 'O'), ('healthy', 'O'), ('condition', 'O'), ('indefinitely', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('but', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('unsure', 'O'), ('nature', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('theory', 'O'), ('has', 'O'), ('him', 'O'), ('decide', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('spend', 'O'), ('his', 'O'), ('final', 'O'), ('hours', 'O'), ('finding', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('man', 'O'), ('who', 'O'), ('killed', 'O'), ('him', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('Upon', 'O'), ('returning', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('Randi', 'PERSON'), ("'s", 'O'), ('home', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('they', 'O'), ('find', 'O'), ('Doug', 'PERSON'), ('dead', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('having', 'O'), ('been', 'O'), ('suspended', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('drowned', 'O'), ('in', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('fish', 'O'), ('tank', 'O'), ('for', 'O'), ('some', 'O'), ('time', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('Roger', 'PERSON'), ('confronts', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('head', 'O'), ('coroner', 'O'), ('Dr.', 'O'), ('Ernest', 'PERSON'), ('McNab', 'PERSON'), ('(', 'O'), ('Darren', 'PERSON'), ('McGavin', 'PERSON'), (')', 'O'), ('who', 'O'), ('was', 'O'), ('indicated', 'O'), ('by', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('secret', 'O'), ('numeric', 'O'), ('code', 'O'), ('that', 'O'), ('Roger', 'PERSON'), ('had', 'O'), ('found', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('but', 'O'), ('he', 'O'), ('turns', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('tables', 'O'), ('on', 'O'), ('Roger', 'PERSON'), (',', 'O'), ('capturing', 'O'), ('him', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('then', 'O'), ('locking', 'O'), ('him', 'O'), ('in', 'O'), ('an', 'O'), ('ambulance', 'O'), ('with', 'O'), ('Rebecca', 'PERSON'), ("'s", 'O'), ('dead', 'O'), ('body', 'O'), ('in', 'O'), ('order', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('wait', 'O'), ('out', 'O'), ('his', 'O'), ('last', 'O'), ('hour', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('dissolution', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('Mortis', 'O'), ('breaks', 'O'), ('in', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('ensuing', 'O'), ('crossfire', 'O'), ('between', 'O'), ('him', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('McNab', 'PERSON'), ("'s", 'O'), ('men', 'O'), ('kill', 'O'), ('off', 'O'), ('most', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('rich', 'O'), ('clients', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('leaving', 'O'), ('Laudermilk', 'PERSON'), ('cowering', 'O'), ('in', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('corner', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('But', 'O'), ('because', 'O'), ('he', 'O'), ("'s", 'O'), ('been', 'O'), ('dead', 'O'), ('for', 'O'), ('hours', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('brain', 'O'), ('deterioration', 'O'), ('leaves', 'O'), ('him', 'O'), ('little', 'O'), ('more', 'O'), ('than', 'O'), ('an', 'O'), ('obedient', 'O'), ('zombie', 'O'), ('with', 'O'), ('no', 'O'), ('memory', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('who', 'O'), ('Roger', 'PERSON'), ('is', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('Before', 'O'), ('he', 'O'), ('can', 'O'), ('obey', 'O'), ('McNab', 'PERSON'), ("'s", 'O'), ('orders', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('kill', 'O'), ('Mortis', 'O'), ('however', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('Roger', 'PERSON'), ('manages', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('trigger', 'O'), ('Doug', 'PERSON'), ("'s", 'O'), ('short', 'O'), ('term', 'O'), ('memory', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('bring', 'O'), ('him', 'O'), ('back', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('normal', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('Roger', 'PERSON'), ('says', 'O'), ('finally', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('``', 'O'), ('This', 'O'), ('could', 'O'), ('be', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('end', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('beautiful', 'O'), ('friendship', 'O'), ('.', 'O'), ("''", 'O')]
[('*', 'O'), ("''", 'O'), ('Creature', 'O'), ('with', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('Atom', 'O'), ('Brain', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ("''", 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('1955', 'O'), ('film', 'O'), ('featuring', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('gangster', 'O'), ('who', 'O'), ('creates', 'O'), ('zombies', 'O'), ('from', 'O'), ('dead', 'O'), ('criminals', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('commit', 'O'), ('crimes', 'O'), ('for', 'O'), ('him', 'O')]
[('*', 'O')]
[('*', 'O')]
[('*', 'O')]
[('*', 'O')]
[("'", 'O'), ("''", 'O'), ("''Una", 'O'), ('de', 'O'), ('zombis', 'O'), ("''", 'O'), ("'", 'O'), ("''", 'O'), ('is', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('2003', 'O'), ('Spanish', 'O'), ('film', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('Outside', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('he', 'O'), ('meets', 'O'), ('Jon', 'PERSON'), (',', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('skilled', 'O'), ('shooter', 'O'), ('who', 'O'), ('decides', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('help', 'O'), ('Fred', 'PERSON'), ('escape', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('city', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('Fortunately', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('he', 'O'), ('manages', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('recover', 'O'), ('his', 'O'), ('walker', 'O'), ('from', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('nurse', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('kill', 'O'), ('numerous', 'O'), ('zombies', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('though', 'O'), ('he', 'O'), ('is', 'O'), ('unable', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('finish', 'O'), ('off', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('nurse', 'O'), ('herself', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('Jon', 'PERSON'), ('attempts', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('kill', 'O'), ('him', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('but', 'O'), ('is', 'O'), ('surrounded', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('eaten', 'O'), ('by', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('zombies', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('Benjamin', 'PERSON'), ('tries', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('bring', 'O'), ('her', 'O'), ('back', 'O'), ('despite', 'O'), ('her', 'O'), ('infection', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('but', 'O'), ('is', 'O'), ('attacked', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('killed', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('while', 'O'), ('another', 'O'), ('zombie', 'O'), ('decapitates', 'O'), ('his', 'O'), ('wife', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('Though', 'O'), ('both', 'O'), ('Hac', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('Mac', 'O'), ('die', 'O'), ('before', 'O'), ('learning', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('truth', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('Mac', 'O'), ("'s", 'O'), ('belief', 'O'), ('turns', 'O'), ('out', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('be', 'O'), ('correct', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('Steve', 'PERSON'), ('Barton', 'PERSON'), ('of', 'O'), ('Dread', 'O'), ('Central', 'O'), ('rated', 'O'), ('it', 'O'), ('55', 'O'), ('stars', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('described', 'O'), ('it', 'O'), ('as', 'O'), ('``', 'O'), ('blood-splattered', 'O'), ('blast', 'O'), ('from', 'O'), ('beginning', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('end', 'O'), ('that', 'O'), ("'s", 'O'), ('heavy', 'O'), ('on', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('sick', 'O'), ("''", 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('Scot', 'PERSON'), ('Weinberg', 'PERSON'), ('of', 'O'), ('DVD', 'O'), ('Talk', 'O'), ('rated', 'O'), ('it', 'O'), ('3.55', 'O'), ('stars', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('wrote', 'O'), ('that', 'O'), ('it', 'O'), ('has', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('``', 'O'), ('fun', 'O'), ('concept', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('clever', 'O'), ('execution', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('unique', 'O'), ('animation', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('tons', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('gooey', 'O'), ('gore', 'O'), ("''", 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('The', 'O'), ('reports', 'O'), ('indicate', 'O'), ('that', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('symptom', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('said', 'O'), ('outbreak', 'O'), ('is', 'O'), ('``', 'O'), ('murder', 'O'), ("''", 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('*', 'O'), ('According', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('Something', 'O'), ('Awful', 'O'), ("'s", 'O'), ('Movie', 'O'), ('Review', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('director', 'O'), ('``', 'O'), ('Vince', 'PERSON'), ("D'Amato", 'PERSON'), ('took', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('premise', 'O'), ('that', 'O'), ('was', 'O'), ('basically', 'O'), ('guaranteed', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('make', 'O'), ('his', 'O'), ('movie', 'O'), ('an', 'O'), ('instant', 'O'), ('hit', 'O'), ('with', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('indie', 'O'), ('horror', 'O'), ('crowd', 'O'), ('in', 'O'), ('spite', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('his', 'O'), ('nonexistent', 'O'), ('budget', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('he', 'O'), ('fucked', 'O'), ('it', 'O'), ('until', 'O'), ('it', 'O'), ('bled', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('The', 'O'), ('resulting', 'O'), ('wretched', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('scarred', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('abused', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('tortured', 'O'), ('rape', 'O'), ('victim', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('movie', 'O'), ('is', 'O'), ('an', 'O'), ('unwatchable', 'O'), ('seventy', 'O'), ('minutes', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('shattered', 'O'), ('homes', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('broken', 'O'), ('dreams', 'O'), ('.', 'O'), ("''", 'O')]
[('The', 'O'), ('plot', 'O'), ('follows', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('disgruntled', 'O'), ('scientist', 'O'), ('who', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('having', 'O'), ('been', 'O'), ('fired', 'O'), ('by', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('space', 'O'), ('agency', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('decides', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('create', 'O'), ('superhuman', 'O'), ('monsters', 'O'), ('from', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('body', 'O'), ('parts', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('innocent', 'O'), ('murder', 'O'), ('victims', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('The', 'O'), ('creatures', 'O'), ('eventually', 'O'), ('escape', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('go', 'O'), ('on', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('killing', 'O'), ('spree', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('attracting', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('attention', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('both', 'O'), ('an', 'O'), ('international', 'O'), ('spy', 'O'), ('ring', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('CIA', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('.', 'O')]
[('The', 'O'), ('story', 'O'), ('is', 'O'), ('about', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('young', 'O'), ('novelist', 'O'), ("'s", 'O'), ('discovery', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('writings', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('late', 'O'), ('scientist', 'O'), ('who', 'O'), ('had', 'O'), ('found', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('means', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('reviving', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('dead', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('In', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('basement', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('further', 'O'), ('digging', 'O'), ('reveals', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('rotted', 'O'), ('corpse', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('with', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('nearby', 'O'), ('wallet', 'O'), ('identifying', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('dead', 'O'), ('man', 'O'), ('as', 'O'), ('Paolo', 'PERSON'), ('Zeder', 'PERSON'), ('.', 'O')]
[('As', 'O'), ('he', 'O'), ('reads', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('ribbon', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('he', 'O'), ('finds', 'O'), ('it', 'O'), ('is', 'O'), ('an', 'O'), ('essay', 'O'), ('written', 'O'), ('by', 'O'), ('scientist', 'O'), ('Paolo', 'PERSON'), ('Zeder', 'PERSON'), ('discussing', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('existence', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('K-Zones-areas', 'O'), ('where', 'O'), ('death', 'O'), ('ceases', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('exist', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('According', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('Zeder', 'PERSON'), ("'s", 'O'), ('essay', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('bodies', 'O'), ('buried', 'O'), ('in', 'O'), ('these', 'O'), ('zones', 'O'), ('can', 'O'), ('return', 'O'), ('from', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('dead', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('Stefano', 'PERSON'), ('sneaks', 'O'), ('onto', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('property', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('discovers', 'O'), ('surveillance', 'O'), ('equipment', 'O'), ('with', 'O'), ('numerous', 'O'), ('monitors', 'O'), ('showing', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('dead', 'O'), ('face', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('man', 'O'), ('buried', 'O'), ('in', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('coffin', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('The', 'O'), ('dead', 'O'), ('man', 'O'), ('is', 'O'), ('Don', 'PERSON'), ('Luigi', 'PERSON'), ('Costa', 'PERSON'), (',', 'O'), ('an', 'O'), ('ex-priest', 'O'), ('who', 'O'), ('abandoned', 'O'), ('his', 'O'), ('vows', 'O'), ('after', 'O'), ('contracting', 'O'), ('an', 'O'), ('incurable', 'O'), ('disease', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('Continuing', 'O'), ('Zeder', 'PERSON'), ("'s", 'O'), ('work', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('Costa', 'O'), ('had', 'O'), ('himself', 'O'), ('buried', 'O'), ('on', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('property', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('suspected', 'O'), ('K-Zone', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('his', 'O'), ('rebirth', 'O'), ('from', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('dead', 'O'), ('is', 'O'), ('caught', 'O'), ('on', 'O'), ('camera', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('Stefano', 'PERSON'), ('manages', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('elude', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('conspirators', 'O'), ('involved', 'O'), ('in', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('experimental', 'O'), ('work', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('but', 'O'), ('finds', 'O'), ('his', 'O'), ('wife', 'O'), ('has', 'O'), ('been', 'O'), ('murdered', 'O'), ('by', 'O'), ('them', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('The', 'O'), ('film', 'O'), ('focuses', 'O'), ('on', 'O'), ('two', 'O'), ('protagonists', 'O'), ('who', 'O'), ('are', 'O'), ('harassed', 'O'), ('by', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('local', 'O'), ('police', 'O'), ('investigator', 'O'), ('in', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('English', 'O'), ('countryside', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('are', 'O'), ('implicated', 'O'), ('in', 'O'), ('murders', 'O'), ('committed', 'O'), ('by', 'O'), ('zombies', 'O'), ('who', 'O'), ('have', 'O'), ('been', 'O'), ('brought', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('life', 'O'), ('by', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('farming', 'O'), ('tool', 'O'), ('designed', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('kill', 'O'), ('insects', 'O'), ('via', 'O'), ('ultra-sonic', 'O'), ('radiation', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('George', 'PERSON'), ('agrees', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('but', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('two', 'O'), ('come', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('dead', 'O'), ('end', 'O'), ('road', 'O'), ('alongside', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('river', 'O'), ('while', 'O'), ('searching', 'O'), ('for', 'O'), ('Edna', 'PERSON'), ("'s", 'O'), ('sister', 'O'), ("'s", 'O'), ('house', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('While', 'O'), ('asking', 'O'), ('for', 'O'), ('directions', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('he', 'O'), ('inquires', 'O'), ('about', 'O'), ('their', 'O'), ('machinery', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('which', 'O'), ('they', 'O'), ('explain', 'O'), ('is', 'O'), ('designed', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('kill', 'O'), ('insects', 'O'), ('through', 'O'), ('ultra-sonic', 'O'), ('radiation', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('When', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('three', 'O'), ('report', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('death', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('aggressive', 'O'), ('police', 'O'), ('sergeant', 'O'), ('thinks', 'O'), ('that', 'O'), ('Katie', 'PERSON'), ('did', 'O'), ('it', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('Back', 'O'), ('at', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('chemist', 'O'), ("'s", 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('they', 'O'), ('collect', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('photos', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('but', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('dead', 'O'), ('man', 'O'), ('does', 'O'), ('not', 'O'), ('appear', 'O'), ('in', 'O'), ('any', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('pictures', 'O'), (';', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('man', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('it', 'O'), ('turns', 'O'), ('out', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('is', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('local', 'O'), ('vagrant', 'O'), ('who', 'O'), ('drowned', 'O'), ('in', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('river', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('Following', 'O'), ('noises', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('crypt', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('they', 'O'), ('come', 'O'), ('across', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('murdered', 'O'), ('man', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('are', 'O'), ('locked', 'O'), ('in', 'O'), ('by', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('vagrant', 'O'), ('zombie', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('who', 'O'), ('brings', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('other', 'O'), ('bodies', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('life', 'O'), ('by', 'O'), ('touching', 'O'), ('their', 'O'), ('eyes', 'O'), ('with', 'O'), ('his', 'O'), ('blood-stained', 'O'), ('fingers', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('They', 'O'), ('lock', 'O'), ('themselves', 'O'), ('in', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('room', 'O'), ('but', 'O'), ('are', 'O'), ('trapped', 'O'), ('there', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('Craig', 'PERSON'), ('soon', 'O'), ('finds', 'O'), ('that', 'O'), ('his', 'O'), ('gun', 'O'), ('is', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('no', 'O'), ('use', 'O'), ('against', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('zombies', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('The', 'O'), ('dead', 'O'), ('break', 'O'), ('into', 'O'), ('their', 'O'), ('room', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('in', 'O'), ('desperation', 'O'), ('George', 'PERSON'), ('throws', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('lit', 'O'), ('oil', 'O'), ('lamp', 'O'), ('at', 'O'), ('them', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('The', 'O'), ('sergeant', 'O'), ('has', 'O'), ('found', 'O'), ('Craig', 'PERSON'), ('and', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('caretaker', 'O'), ("'s", 'O'), ('bodies', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('thinking', 'O'), ('they', 'O'), ('may', 'O'), ('be', 'O'), ('devil', 'O'), ('worshippers', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('issues', 'O'), ('orders', 'O'), ('``', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('shoot', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('kill', 'O'), ("''", 'O'), ('George', 'PERSON'), ('and', 'O'), ('Edna', 'PERSON'), ('.', 'O')]
[('In', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('field', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('machine', 'O'), ('is', 'O'), ('repaired', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('switched', 'O'), ('on', 'O'), ('again', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('which', 'O'), ('brings', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('life', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('number', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('bodies', 'O'), ('in', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('nearby', 'O'), ('morgue', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('George', 'PERSON'), ('escapes', 'O'), ('in', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('police', 'O'), ('car', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('finds', 'O'), ('Edna', 'PERSON'), ('has', 'O'), ('been', 'O'), ('taken', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('hospital', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('where', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('local', 'O'), ('morgue', 'O'), ('is', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('She', 'O'), ('is', 'O'), ('being', 'O'), ('sedated', 'O'), ('while', 'O'), ('George', 'PERSON'), ('is', 'O'), ('now', 'O'), ('being', 'O'), ('chased', 'O'), ('by', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('police', 'O'), ('as', 'O'), ('he', 'O'), ('drives', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('hospital', 'O'), ('where', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('zombies', 'O'), ('are', 'O'), ('now', 'O'), ('killing', 'O'), ('people', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('including', 'O'), ('Katie', 'PERSON'), ('who', 'O'), ('as', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('zombie', 'O'), ('tries', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('kill', 'O'), ('her', 'O'), ('sister', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('George', 'PERSON'), ('arrives', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('starts', 'O'), ('setting', 'O'), ('fire', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('zombies', 'O'), ('but', 'O'), ('it', 'O'), ('turns', 'O'), ('out', 'O'), ('that', 'O'), ('he', 'O'), ('was', 'O'), ('too', 'O'), ('late', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('save', 'O'), ('Edna', 'PERSON'), ('and', 'O'), ('as', 'O'), ('she', 'O'), ('suddenly', 'O'), ('attacks', 'O'), ('him', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('he', 'O'), ('pushes', 'O'), ('her', 'O'), ('into', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('room', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('which', 'O'), ('is', 'O'), ('now', 'O'), ('burning', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('*', 'O')]
[('*', 'O')]
[('*', 'O')]
[('|', 'O'), ('cinematography', 'O'), ('=', 'O'), ('Matthew', 'PERSON'), ('M.', 'PERSON'), ('Howe', 'PERSON')]
[('|', 'O'), ('music', 'O'), ('=', 'O')]
[('|', 'O'), ('distributor', 'O'), ('=', 'O'), ('Tempe', 'O'), ('Video', 'O')]
[('|', 'O'), ('released', 'O'), ('=', 'O')]
[('|', 'O'), ('runtime', 'O'), ('=', 'O'), ('84', 'O'), ('minutes', 'O')]
[('|', 'O'), ('language', 'O'), ('=', 'O'), ('English', 'O')]
[('|', 'O'), ('country', 'O'), ('=', 'O'), ('United', 'LOCATION'), ('States', 'LOCATION')]
[('|', 'O'), ('budget', 'O'), ('=', 'O')]
[('}', 'O'), ('}', 'O')]
[("'", 'O'), ("''", 'O'), ("''Shatter", 'O'), ('Dead', 'O'), ("''", 'O'), ("'", 'O'), ("''", 'O'), ('is', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('zombie', 'O'), ('film', 'O'), ('set', 'O'), ('in', 'O'), ('an', 'O'), ('unknown', 'O'), ('area', 'O'), ('following', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('woman', 'O'), ('named', 'O'), ('Susan', 'PERSON'), ("'s", 'O'), ('(', 'O'), ('Stark', 'O'), ('Raven', 'O'), (')', 'O'), ('attempt', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('return', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('apartment', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('her', 'O'), ('boyfriend', 'O'), ('(', 'O'), ('Daniel', 'PERSON'), ("'Smalls", 'O'), ("'", 'O'), ('Johnson', 'PERSON'), (')', 'O'), ('in', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('midst', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('return', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('dead', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('semblance', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('life', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('On', 'O'), ('her', 'O'), ('way', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('she', 'O'), ('is', 'O'), ('harassed', 'O'), ('by', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('preacher', 'O'), ('(', 'O'), ('Robert', 'PERSON'), ('Wells', 'PERSON'), (')', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('dead', 'O'), ('woman', 'O'), ('named', 'O'), ('Mary', 'PERSON'), ('(', 'O'), ('Flora', 'LOCATION'), ('Fauna', 'LOCATION'), (')', 'O'), ('intent', 'O'), ('on', 'O'), ('convincing', 'O'), ('her', 'O'), ('that', 'O'), ('being', 'O'), ('undead', 'O'), ('is', 'O'), ('preferable', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('life', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('The', 'O'), ('back', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('DVD', 'O'), ('cover', 'O'), ('says', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('Angel', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('Death', 'O'), ('impregnates', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('mortal', 'O'), ('woman', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('causing', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('dead', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('come', 'O'), ('alive', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('She', 'O'), ('encounters', 'O'), ('some', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('living', 'O'), ('dead', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('including', 'O'), ('one', 'O'), ('who', 'O'), ('gave', 'O'), ('up', 'O'), ('his', 'O'), ('arm', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('research', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('She', 'O'), ('holds', 'O'), ('him', 'O'), ('at', 'O'), ('gun', 'O'), ('point', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('holds', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('mirror', 'O'), ('under', 'O'), ('his', 'O'), ('nose', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('While', 'O'), ('staying', 'O'), ('there', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('she', 'O'), ('encounters', 'O'), ('Mary', 'PERSON'), (',', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('dead', 'O'), ('woman', 'O'), ('pretending', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('be', 'O'), ('alive', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('they', 'O'), ('shower', 'O'), ('together', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('This', 'O'), ('group', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('Zombies', 'O'), ('believes', 'O'), ('these', 'O'), ('are', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('end', 'O'), ('times', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('God', 'O'), ('will', 'O'), ('return', 'O'), ('once', 'O'), ('humanity', 'O'), ('is', 'O'), ('all', 'O'), ('dead', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('Susan', 'PERSON'), ('watches', 'O'), ('as', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('newly', 'O'), ('dead', 'O'), ('mother', 'O'), ('begins', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('nurse', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('newly', 'O'), ('dead', 'O'), ('fetus', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('She', 'O'), ('threatens', 'O'), ('him', 'O'), ('while', 'O'), ('he', 'O'), ('tries', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('convince', 'O'), ('her', 'O'), ('that', 'O'), ('death', 'O'), ('is', 'O'), ('better', 'O'), ('than', 'O'), ('life', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('He', 'O'), ("'s", 'O'), ('also', 'O'), ('killed', 'O'), ('himself', 'O'), ('but', 'O'), ('is', 'O'), ('up', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('about', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('He', 'O'), ('kept', 'O'), ('hearing', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('phone', 'O'), ('ringing', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('hearing', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('dead', 'O'), ('talking', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('him', 'O'), ('(', 'O'), ('including', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('cremated', 'O'), ('mother', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('sister', 'O'), ('who', 'O'), ('never', 'O'), ('even', 'O'), ('knew', 'O'), ('how', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('use', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('phone', 'O'), ('.', 'O'), (')', 'O')]
[('They', 'O'), ('ca', 'O'), ("n't", 'O'), ('have', 'O'), ('sex', 'O'), ('because', 'O'), ('he', 'O'), ('has', 'O'), ('no', 'O'), ('blood', 'O'), ('pressure', 'O'), ('(', 'O'), ('his', 'O'), ('blood', 'O'), ('is', 'O'), ('in', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('bathtub', 'O'), ('after', 'O'), ('all', 'O'), (')', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('so', 'O'), ('they', 'O'), ('have', 'O'), ('intercourse', 'O'), ('using', 'O'), ('her', 'O'), ('gun', 'O'), ('as', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('strap-on', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('He', 'O'), ('slips', 'O'), ('poison', 'O'), ('into', 'O'), ('her', 'O'), ('milk', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('He', 'O'), ('wants', 'O'), ('her', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('be', 'O'), ('dead', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('beautiful', 'O'), ('forever', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('The', 'O'), ('last', 'O'), ('sequence', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('film', 'O'), ('is', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('montage', 'O'), ('switching', 'O'), ('back', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('forth', 'O'), ('between', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('preacher', 'O'), ('making', 'O'), ('splints', 'O'), ('for', 'O'), ('her', 'O'), ('boyfriend', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('Susan', 'PERSON'), ('putting', 'O'), ('tears', 'O'), ('in', 'O'), ('her', 'O'), ('eyes', 'O'), ('from', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('faucet', 'O'), ('so', 'O'), ('she', 'O'), ('can', 'O'), ('mourn', 'O'), ('her', 'O'), ('own', 'O'), ('death', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('During', 'O'), ('dinner', 'O'), ('at', 'O'), ('Renee', 'PERSON'), ("'s", 'O'), ('house', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('place', 'O'), ('comes', 'O'), ('under', 'O'), ('siege', 'O'), ('by', 'O'), ('ancient', 'O'), ('Mayan', 'O'), ('zombies', 'O'), ('who', 'O'), ('Michael', 'PERSON'), ('had', 'O'), ('killed', 'O'), ('in', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('past', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('The', 'O'), ('dead', 'O'), ('orphan', 'O'), ('connects', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('Renee', 'PERSON'), ('who', 'O'), ('feels', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('need', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('solve', 'O'), ('why', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('ancient', 'O'), ('Mayan', 'O'), ('Zombies', 'O'), ('were', 'O'), ('killed', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('how', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('rest', 'O'), ('their', 'O'), ('souls', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('It', 'O'), ('also', 'O'), ('received', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('limited', 'O'), ('theatrical', 'O'), ('run', 'O'), ('in', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('U.S', 'LOCATION'), ('.', 'O')]
[('For', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('past', 'O'), ('13', 'O'), ('years', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('Dr.', 'O'), ('Herbert', 'PERSON'), ('West', 'PERSON'), ('(', 'O'), ('Jeffrey', 'PERSON'), ('Combs', 'PERSON'), (')', 'O'), ('has', 'O'), ('been', 'O'), ('serving', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('prison', 'O'), ('sentence', 'O'), ('due', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('murder', 'O'), ('at', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('hands', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('one', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('his', 'O'), ('zombies', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('The', 'O'), ('capsule', 'O'), ('can', 'O'), ('then', 'O'), ('be', 'O'), ('connected', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('corpse', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('used', 'O'), ('in', 'O'), ('conjunction', 'O'), ('with', 'O'), ('West', 'O'), ("'s", 'O'), ('previously', 'O'), ('developed', 'O'), ('reagent', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('restore', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('former', 'O'), ('dead', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('lifelike', 'O'), ('state', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('It', 'O'), ('is', 'O'), ('revealed', 'O'), ('that', 'O'), ('Phillips', 'PERSON'), ('is', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('younger', 'O'), ('brother', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('teenage', 'O'), ('girl', 'O'), ('who', 'O'), ('was', 'O'), ('killed', 'O'), ('by', 'O'), ('West', 'PERSON'), ("'s", 'O'), ('zombie', 'O'), ('(', 'O'), ('he', 'O'), ("'s", 'O'), ('shown', 'O'), ('watching', 'O'), ('West', 'O'), ('being', 'O'), ('taken', 'O'), ('away', 'O'), ('by', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('cops', 'O'), (')', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('came', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('prison', 'O'), ('for', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('explicit', 'O'), ('purpose', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('working', 'O'), ('with', 'O'), ('him', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('Crushed', 'O'), ('by', 'O'), ('Laura', 'PERSON'), ("'s", 'O'), ('death', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('Dr.', 'O'), ('Phillips', 'PERSON'), ('succumbs', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('Dr.', 'O'), ('West', 'PERSON'), ("'s", 'O'), ('wishes', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('his', 'O'), ('experiments', 'O'), ('are', 'O'), ('allowed', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('literally', 'O'), ('take', 'O'), ('on', 'O'), ('new', 'O'), ('life', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('Eventually', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('warden', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('prison', 'O'), ('uncovers', 'O'), ('West', 'O'), ("'s", 'O'), ('experiments', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('moves', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('put', 'O'), ('an', 'O'), ('end', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('them', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('but', 'O'), ('he', 'O'), ('is', 'O'), ('killed', 'O'), ('by', 'O'), ('West', 'PERSON'), (',', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('subsequently', 'O'), ('re-animated', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('Soon', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('it', 'O'), ('is', 'O'), ('unclear', 'O'), ('who', 'O'), ('is', 'O'), ('dead', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('who', 'O'), ('is', 'O'), ('alive', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('who', 'O'), ('has', 'O'), ('been', 'O'), ('exposed', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('agent', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('As', 'O'), ('they', 'O'), ('approach', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('door', 'O'), ('at', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('end', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('corridor', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('one', 'O'), ('prisoner', 'O'), ('seizes', 'O'), ('his', 'O'), ('chance', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('assault', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('guard', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('but', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('door', 'O'), ('opens', 'O'), ('almost', 'O'), ('immediately', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('several', 'O'), ('German', 'O'), ('soldiers', 'O'), ('step', 'O'), ('through', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('mow', 'O'), ('down', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('entire', 'O'), ('group', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('save', 'O'), ('for', 'O'), ('one', 'O'), ('prisoner', 'O'), ('who', 'O'), ('remains', 'O'), ('standing', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('Identifying', 'O'), ('him', 'O'), ('as', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('threat', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('they', 'O'), ('open', 'O'), ('fire', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('but', 'O'), ('as', 'O'), ('they', 'O'), ('investigate', 'O'), ('his', 'O'), ('corpse', 'O'), ('it', 'O'), ('is', 'O'), ('revealed', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('soldier', 'O'), ('is', 'O'), ('one', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('their', 'O'), ('own', 'O'), ('dead', 'O'), ('from', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('previous', 'O'), ('encounter', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('as', 'O'), ('he', 'O'), ('springs', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('life', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('second', 'O'), ('time', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('number', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('zombies', 'O'), ('leap', 'O'), ('into', 'O'), ('action', 'O'), ('from', 'O'), ('their', 'O'), ('hiding', 'O'), ('places', 'O'), ('in', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('trees', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('further', 'O'), ('destroy', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('unit', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('They', 'O'), ('are', 'O'), ('rapidly', 'O'), ('split', 'O'), ('up', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('attacked', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('however', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('with', 'O'), ('Niemi', 'PERSON'), ('being', 'O'), ('bitten', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('then', 'O'), ('killing', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('young', 'O'), ('cameraman', 'O'), ('before', 'O'), ('being', 'O'), ('gunned', 'O'), ('down', 'O'), ('by', 'O'), ('Laakso', 'PERSON'), ('.', 'O')]
[('As', 'O'), ('they', 'O'), ('near', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('exit', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('surface', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('Kolya', 'PERSON'), ('is', 'O'), ('grabbed', 'O'), ('by', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('zombie', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('falls', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('his', 'O'), ('death', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('with', 'O'), ('Laakso', 'PERSON'), ('forced', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('leave', 'O'), ('him', 'O'), ('as', 'O'), ('he', 'O'), ('races', 'O'), ('topside', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('set', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('signal', 'O'), ('flares', 'O'), ('for', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('incoming', 'O'), ('fighter-bombers', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('He', 'O'), ('discloses', 'O'), ('that', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('agent', 'O'), ('in', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('tank', 'O'), ('was', 'O'), ('capable', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('reanimating', 'O'), ('dead', 'O'), ('cells', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('advises', 'O'), ('that', 'O'), ('he', 'O'), ('not', 'O'), ('bother', 'O'), ('with', 'O'), ('evacuation', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('but', 'O'), ('contain', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('incident', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('let', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('National', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Guard', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('deal', 'O'), ('with', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('rest', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('Upon', 'O'), ('finding', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('second', 'O'), ('van', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('containing', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('Prisoner', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('Morty', 'PERSON'), ('finds', 'O'), ('Bottin', 'PERSON'), ('and', 'O'), ('Savini', 'PERSON'), ('are', 'O'), ('dead', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('more', 'O'), ('zombies', 'O'), ('are', 'O'), ('coming', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('After', 'O'), ('turning', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('power', 'O'), ('on', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('several', 'O'), ('zombies', 'O'), ('break', 'O'), ('in', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('nearly', 'O'), ('kill', 'O'), ('Morty', 'PERSON'), (',', 'O'), ('but', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('Prisoner', 'O'), ('saves', 'O'), ('him', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('The', 'O'), ('professor', 'O'), ('also', 'O'), ('chooses', 'O'), ('death', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('by', 'O'), ('Morty', 'PERSON'), ("'s", 'O'), ('gun', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('feeling', 'O'), ('that', 'O'), ('``', 'O'), ('there', 'O'), ('are', 'O'), ('worse', 'O'), ('things', 'O'), ('.', 'O'), ("''", 'O')]
[('The', 'O'), ('three', 'O'), ('proceed', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('kill', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('zombies', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('while', 'O'), ('Morty', 'PERSON'), ('escapes', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('train', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('taking', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('gun', 'O'), ('from', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('Prisoner', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('helping', 'O'), ('them', 'O'), ('out', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('Her', 'O'), ('seemingly', 'O'), ('mundane', 'O'), ('day-to-day', 'O'), ('activities', 'O'), ('take', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('strange', 'O'), ('turn', 'O'), ('when', 'O'), ('she', 'O'), ('tries', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('kill', 'O'), ('herself', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[("'", 'O'), ("''", 'O'), ('Zeke', 'O'), ("''", 'O'), ("'", 'O'), (':', 'O'), ('(', 'O'), ('voiced', 'O'), ('by', 'O'), ('John', 'PERSON'), ('DiMaggio', 'PERSON'), (')', 'O'), ('A', 'O'), ('zombie', 'O'), ('who', 'O'), ('becomes', 'O'), ('Scott', 'PERSON'), ("'s", 'O'), ('friend', 'O'), ('after', 'O'), ('trying', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('kill', 'O'), ('him', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('He', 'O'), ('does', 'O'), ("n't", 'O'), ('have', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('body', 'O'), ('but', 'O'), ('he', 'O'), ('manages', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('walk', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('do', 'O'), ('manual', 'O'), ('activities', 'O'), ('with', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('intestines', 'O'), ('sticking', 'O'), ('out', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('his', 'O'), ('neck', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('After', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('successful', 'O'), ('hunt', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('he', 'O'), ('is', 'O'), ('robbed', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('left', 'O'), ('for', 'O'), ('dead', 'O'), ('by', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('rival', 'O'), ('gang', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('hunters', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('led', 'O'), ('by', 'O'), ('Blythe', 'PERSON'), ('Remington', 'PERSON'), ('(', 'O'), ('Parrish', 'PERSON'), ('Randall', 'PERSON'), (')', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('who', 'O'), ('plans', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('spread', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('plague', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('creating', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('larger', 'O'), ('bounty', 'O'), ('market', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('After', 'O'), ('Renchard', 'PERSON'), ('and', 'O'), ('Brianna', 'PERSON'), ('flee', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('city', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('Mike', 'PERSON'), ('(', 'O'), ('Ryan', 'PERSON'), ('Lloyd', 'PERSON'), (')', 'O'), ('is', 'O'), ('killed', 'O'), ('in', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('sewers', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('Vincent', 'PERSON'), ('(', 'O'), ('Geoff', 'PERSON'), ('Meed', 'PERSON'), (')', 'O'), ('shoots', 'O'), ('Renchard', 'PERSON'), ('and', 'O'), ('captures', 'O'), ('Brianna', 'PERSON'), ('.', 'O')]
[('He', 'O'), ('tells', 'O'), ('Renchard', 'PERSON'), ('he', 'O'), ('did', 'O'), ('it', 'O'), ('because', 'O'), ('he', 'O'), ('liked', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('world', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('way', 'O'), ('it', 'O'), ('was', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('leaves', 'O'), ('him', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('die', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('After', 'O'), ('finding', 'O'), ('them', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('Renchard', 'PERSON'), ('kills', 'O'), ('Vincent', 'PERSON'), (',', 'O'), ('who', 'O'), ('was', 'O'), ('attempting', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('rape', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('kill', 'O'), ('Brianna', 'PERSON'), ('.', 'O')]
[('A', 'O'), ('new', 'O'), ('Lordi', 'PERSON'), ('song', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ("''Beast", 'O'), ('Loose', 'O'), ('in', 'O'), ('Paradise', 'O'), ("''", 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('is', 'O'), ('featured', 'O'), ('in', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('end', 'O'), ('credits', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('film', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('A', 'O'), ('young', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('autistic', 'O'), ('girl', 'O'), ('at', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('hospital', 'O'), ('holds', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('key', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('defeating', 'O'), ('other-dimensional', 'O'), ('monsters', 'O'), ('that', 'O'), ('seek', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('kill', 'O'), ('everyone', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('One', 'O'), ('day', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('they', 'O'), ('murder', 'O'), ('their', 'O'), ('boss', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('dump', 'O'), ('his', 'O'), ('body', 'O'), ('on', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('Tokyo', 'LOCATION'), ('toxic', 'O'), ('waste', 'O'), ('dump', 'O'), ('known', 'O'), ('as', 'O'), ('``', 'O'), ('Black', 'O'), ('Fuji', 'O'), ("''", 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('Things', 'O'), ('suddenly', 'O'), ('become', 'O'), ('worse', 'O'), ('when', 'O'), ('an', 'O'), ('army', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('undead', 'O'), ('rises', 'O'), ('from', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('waste', 'O'), ('dump', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('begin', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('attack', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('living', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('In', 'O'), ('an', 'O'), ('attempt', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('take', 'O'), ('out', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('mysterious', 'O'), ('priest', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('lone', 'O'), ('samurai', 'O'), ('charges', 'O'), ('full', 'O'), ('scale', 'O'), ('but', 'O'), ('is', 'O'), ('easily', 'O'), ('killed', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('defeated', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('The', 'O'), ('zombies', 'O'), ('are', 'O'), ('killed', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('Prisoner', 'O'), ('KSC2-303', 'O'), ('escapes', 'O'), ('back', 'O'), ('into', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('forest', 'O'), ('with', 'O'), ('The', 'O'), ('Girl', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('Prisoner', 'O'), ('KSC2-303', 'O'), ('steals', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('dead', 'O'), ('man', 'O'), ("'s", 'O'), ('clothes', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('is', 'O'), ('confronted', 'O'), ('by', 'O'), ('one', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('Yakuza', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('The', 'O'), ('corpses', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('all', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('men', 'O'), ('they', 'O'), ('have', 'O'), ('killed', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('buried', 'O'), ('in', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('forest', 'O'), ('come', 'O'), ('back', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('life', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('attack', 'O'), ('them', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('The', 'O'), ('Yakuza', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('Assassins', 'O'), ('take', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('upper', 'O'), ('hand', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('kill', 'O'), ('him', 'O'), ('first', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('One', 'O'), ('is', 'O'), ('defeated', 'O'), ('by', 'O'), ('The', 'O'), ('Girl', 'O'), ('with', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('log', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('other', 'O'), ('is', 'O'), ('confronted', 'O'), ('by', 'O'), ('The', 'O'), ('Man', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('killed', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('Unable', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('accept', 'O'), ('his', 'O'), ('explanations', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('Prisoner', 'O'), ('KSC2-303', 'O'), ('attempts', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('kill', 'O'), ('The', 'O'), ('Man', 'O'), ('but', 'O'), ('is', 'O'), ('killed', 'O'), ('himself', 'O'), ('instead', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('*Tak', 'O'), ('Sakaguchi', 'PERSON'), ('as', 'O'), ('Prisoner', 'O'), ('KSC2-303', 'O')]
[('*Hideo', 'O'), ('Sakaki', 'PERSON'), ('as', 'O'), ('The', 'O'), ('Man', 'O')]
[('*Chieko', 'O'), ('Misaka', 'PERSON'), ('as', 'O'), ('The', 'O'), ('Girl', 'O')]
[('*Kenji', 'O'), ('Matsuda', 'PERSON'), ('as', 'O'), ('Yakuza', 'O'), ('Leader', 'O'), ('with', 'O'), ('butterfly', 'O'), ('knife', 'O')]
[('*Yuichiro', 'O'), ('Arai', 'PERSON'), ('as', 'O'), ('Motorcycle-riding', 'O'), ('yakuza', 'O'), ('with', 'O'), ('revolver', 'O')]
[('*Minoru', 'O'), ('Matsumoto', 'PERSON'), ('as', 'O'), ('Crazy', 'O'), ('yakuza', 'O'), ('with', 'O'), ('amulet', 'O')]
[('*Kazuhito', 'O'), ('Ohba', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('as', 'O'), ('Yakuza', 'O'), ('with', 'O'), ('glasses', 'O')]
[('*Takehiro', 'O'), ('Katayama', 'PERSON'), ('as', 'O'), ('Red-haired', 'O'), ('assassin', 'O')]
[('*Ayumi', 'O'), ('Yoshihara', 'PERSON'), ('as', 'O'), ('Long-haired', 'O'), ('female', 'O'), ('assassin', 'O')]
[('*Shoichiro', 'O'), ('Masumoto', 'PERSON'), ('as', 'O'), ('One-handed', 'O'), ('cop', 'O')]
[('*Toshiro', 'O'), ('Kamiaka', 'PERSON'), ('as', 'O'), ('Samurai', 'O'), ('warrior', 'O')]
[('*Yukihito', 'O'), ('Tanikado', 'O'), ('as', 'O'), ('Cop', 'O'), ('with', 'O'), ('Barrett', 'PERSON')]
[('*Hoshimi', 'O'), ('Asai', 'PERSON'), ('as', 'O'), ('Short-haired', 'O'), ('female', 'O'), ('assassin', 'O')]
[('*Ryosuke', 'O'), ('Watabe', 'PERSON'), ('as', 'O'), ('Yakuza', 'O'), ('zombie', 'O'), ('in', 'O'), ('alligator-skin', 'O'), ('coat', 'O')]
[('*Motonari', 'O'), ('Komiya', 'PERSON'), ('as', 'O'), ('Other', 'O'), ('prisoner', 'O')]
[('Originally', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ("''Versus", 'O'), ("''", 'O'), ('was', 'O'), ('intended', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('be', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('sequel', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('director', 'O'), ('Kitamura', 'PERSON'), ("'s", 'O'), ('``', 'O'), ('amateur', 'O'), ("''", 'O'), ('short', 'O'), ('film', 'O'), ("'", 'O'), ("''", 'O'), ("''Down", 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('Hell', 'O'), ("''", 'O'), ("'", 'O'), ("''", 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('with', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('intention', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('also', 'O'), ('shooting', 'O'), ("''Versus", 'O'), ("''", 'O'), ('on', 'O'), ('video', 'O'), ('with', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('low', 'O'), ('budget', 'O'), ('as', 'O'), ('he', 'O'), ('did', 'O'), ('with', 'O'), ("''Down", 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('Hell', 'O'), ("''", 'O'), ('but', 'O'), ('instead', 'O'), ('decided', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('shoot', 'O'), ('on', 'O'), ('film', 'O'), ('with', 'O'), ('budget', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('$', 'O'), ('10,000', 'O'), ('for', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('theatrical', 'O'), ('release', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('The', 'O'), ('film', 'O'), ('did', 'O'), ('not', 'O'), ('receive', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('title', 'O'), ("''Versus", 'O'), ("''", 'O'), ('until', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('end', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('shooting', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('In', 'O'), ('fact', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('friend', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('Kitamura', 'PERSON'), ("'s", 'O'), ('(', 'O'), ('who', 'O'), ('would', 'O'), ('end', 'O'), ('up', 'O'), ('working', 'O'), ('with', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('director', 'O'), ('as', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('second', 'O'), ('unit', 'O'), ('director', 'O'), ('for', 'O'), ('Godzilla', 'O'), (':', 'O'), ('Final', 'O'), ('Wars', 'O'), (')', 'O'), ('suggested', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('title', 'O'), ("''Versus", 'O'), ("''", 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('reference', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('struggles', 'O'), ('Kitamura', 'PERSON'), ('suffered', 'O'), ('through', 'O'), ('while', 'O'), ('trying', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('launch', 'O'), ('his', 'O'), ('career', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[("''", 'O'), ("''", 'O'), ('I', 'O'), ('did', 'O'), ("n't", 'O'), ('actually', 'O'), ('have', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('title', 'O'), ('Versus', 'O'), ('until', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('very', 'O'), ('end', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('shooting', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('Sight', 'O'), ('&', 'O'), ('Sound', 'O'), ('praised', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('film', 'O'), ('by', 'O'), ('commenting', 'O'), ("''", 'O'), ("''", 'O'), ('With', 'O'), ('Kurosawa-style', 'O'), ('swordplay', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('martial', 'O'), ('arts', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('elaborately', 'O'), ('choreographed', 'O'), ('gun', 'O'), ('battles', 'O'), ("''", 'O'), ("''", 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('Kate', 'PERSON'), ('becomes', 'O'), ('infected', 'O'), ('with', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('disease', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('is', 'O'), ('killed', 'O'), ('by', 'O'), ('April', 'O'), ('when', 'O'), ('she', 'O'), ('tries', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('kill', 'O'), ('Daniel', 'PERSON'), ('.', 'O')]
[('He', 'O'), ('demands', 'O'), ('water', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('teenagers', 'O'), ('tell', 'O'), ('him', 'O'), ('they', 'O'), ('do', 'O'), ("n't", 'O'), ('have', 'O'), ('any', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('he', 'O'), ('retaliates', 'O'), ('by', 'O'), ('showing', 'O'), ('them', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('severed', 'O'), ('head', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('previous', 'O'), ('victim', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('is', 'O'), ('immediately', 'O'), ('kicked', 'O'), ('out', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('van', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('Played', 'O'), ('by', 'O'), ('Sultan', 'PERSON'), ('Billa', 'PERSON'), (',', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('Burqaman', 'O'), ('is', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('large', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('hefty', 'O'), ('butcher', 'O'), ('wielding', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('morning', 'O'), ('star', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('When', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('renegade', 'O'), ('band', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('young', 'O'), ('filmmakers', 'O'), ('break', 'O'), ('into', 'O'), ('an', 'O'), ('abandoned', 'O'), ('hospital', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('make', 'O'), ('their', 'O'), ('horror', 'O'), ('epic', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('they', 'O'), ('stumble', 'O'), ('upon', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('real', 'O'), ('dead', 'O'), ('body', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('decide', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('use', 'O'), ('it', 'O'), ('in', 'O'), ('their', 'O'), ('movie', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('They', 'O'), ('accidentally', 'O'), ('bring', 'O'), ('it', 'O'), ('back', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('life', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('open', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('portal', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('dead', 'O'), ('world', 'O'), ('that', 'O'), ('releases', 'O'), ('dozens', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('other', 'O'), ('zombies', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('then', 'O'), ('struggle', 'O'), ('for', 'O'), ('their', 'O'), ('lives', 'O'), ('in', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('desperate', 'O'), ('attempt', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('flee', 'O'), ('from', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('creatures', 'O'), ('who', 'O'), ('apparently', 'O'), ('have', 'O'), ('them', 'O'), ('hopelessly', 'O'), ('trapped', 'O'), ('in', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('hospital', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[("''eFilmCritic", 'O'), ("''", 'O'), ('found', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('film', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('be', 'O'), ('``', 'O'), ('easily', 'O'), ('one', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('absolute', 'O'), ('worst', 'O'), ('films', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('ever', 'O'), ('smudge', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('rental', 'O'), ('store', 'O'), ('shelf', 'O'), ("''", 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('opining', 'O'), ('that', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('film', 'O'), ("'s", 'O'), ('script', 'O'), ('was', 'O'), ('cliche', 'O'), ("'", 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('unoriginal', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('pacing', 'O'), ('would', 'O'), ('``', 'O'), ('cause', 'O'), ('even', 'O'), ('snails', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('squirm', 'O'), ('with', 'O'), ('impatience', 'O'), ("''", 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('concluding', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('review', 'O'), ('by', 'O'), ('writing', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('film', 'O'), ('was', 'O'), ('``', 'O'), ('horribly', 'O'), ('directed', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('horribly', 'O'), ('shot', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('just', 'O'), ('plain', 'O'), ('horribly', 'O'), ('executed', 'O'), ('.', 'O'), ("''", 'O')]
[('Unwilling', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('give', 'O'), ('up', 'O'), ('what', 'O'), ('she', 'O'), ('believes', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('be', 'O'), ('hers', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('she', 'O'), ('uses', 'O'), ('voodoo', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('resurrect', 'O'), ('her', 'O'), ('dead', 'O'), ('brother', 'O'), ('(', 'O'), ('referred', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('as', 'O'), ('``', 'O'), ("''The", 'O'), ('Dead', 'O'), ('One', 'O'), ("''", 'O'), ("''", 'O'), (')', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('kill', 'O'), ('her', 'O'), ('enemies', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('As', 'O'), ('Chekov', 'PERSON'), ('investigates', 'O'), ('further', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('he', 'O'), ('learns', 'O'), ('that', 'O'), ('Droila', 'PERSON'), ('is', 'O'), ('reanimating', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('dead', 'O'), ('with', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('help', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('necrophiliac', 'O'), ('grave', 'O'), ('robber', 'O'), ('by', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('name', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('Igor', 'PERSON'), ('.', 'O')]
[('In', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('end', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('Droila', 'PERSON'), ("'s", 'O'), ('zombies', 'O'), ('rise', 'O'), ('against', 'O'), ('him', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('Despite', 'O'), ('unplugging', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('television', 'O'), ('set', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('it', 'O'), ('nonetheless', 'O'), ('reactivates', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('spawns', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('film', 'O'), ("'s", 'O'), ('zombies', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('who', 'O'), ('attack', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('kill', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('writer', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('The', 'O'), ('zombies', 'O'), ('kill', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('dog', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('leave', 'O'), ('it', 'O'), ('for', 'O'), ('Jeff', 'PERSON'), ('and', 'O'), ('Zoe', 'PERSON'), ('to', 'O'), ('find', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('follow', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('pair', 'O'), ('back', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('neighborhood', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('That', 'O'), ('afternoon', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('man', 'O'), ('named', 'O'), ('Joshua', 'PERSON'), ('Daniels', 'PERSON'), ('comes', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('their', 'O'), ('front', 'O'), ('door', 'O'), ('looking', 'O'), ('for', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('television', 'O'), ('set', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('claiming', 'O'), ('that', 'O'), ('he', 'O'), ('bought', 'O'), ('it', 'O'), ('at', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('yard', 'O'), ('sale', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('mailed', 'O'), ('it', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('Paranormal', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Institute', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('after', 'O'), ('it', 'O'), ('killed', 'O'), ('his', 'O'), ('wife', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('The', 'O'), ('next', 'O'), ('day', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('zombies', 'O'), ('arrive', 'O'), ('in', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('neighborhood', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('kill', 'O'), ('April', 'O'), ("'s", 'O'), ('father', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('his', 'O'), ('maid', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('their', 'O'), ('next-door', 'O'), ('neighbors', 'O'), ('before', 'O'), ('laying', 'O'), ('siege', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('Zoe', 'PERSON'), ('and', 'O'), ('Jeff', 'PERSON'), ("'s", 'O'), ('house', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('Joshua', 'PERSON'), ('explains', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('psychology', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('zombies', 'O'), (':', 'O'), ('realizing', 'O'), ('that', 'O'), ('they', 'O'), ('are', 'O'), ('in', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('liminal', 'O'), ('state', 'O'), ('between', 'O'), ('life', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('death', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('zombies', 'O'), ('kill', 'O'), ('humans', 'O'), ('out', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('envy', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('The', 'O'), ('zombies', 'O'), ('can', 'O'), ('be', 'O'), ('destroyed', 'O'), ('by', 'O'), ('severely', 'O'), ('wounding', 'O'), ('them', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('thus', 'O'), ('``', 'O'), ('convincing', 'O'), ("''", 'O'), ('them', 'O'), ('that', 'O'), ('they', 'O'), ('are', 'O'), ('dead', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('Joshua', 'PERSON'), ('is', 'O'), ('killed', 'O'), ('when', 'O'), ('an', 'O'), ('arrow', 'O'), ('is', 'O'), ('shoved', 'O'), ('through', 'O'), ('his', 'O'), ('chest', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('Jeff', 'PERSON'), ('gets', 'O'), ('trapped', 'O'), ('in', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('shed', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('where', 'O'), ('he', 'O'), ('discovers', 'O'), ('April', 'O'), ("'s", 'O'), ('now', 'O'), ('lifeless', 'O'), ('body', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('The', 'O'), ('lone', 'O'), ('remaining', 'O'), ('zombie', 'O'), ('wakes', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('other', 'O'), ('zombies', 'O'), ('from', 'O'), ('their', 'O'), ('delusions', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('death', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('zombies', 'O'), ('rise', 'O'), ('up', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('Jeff', 'PERSON'), ('decapitates', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('zombie', 'O'), ('with', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('machete', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('but', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('zombie', 'O'), ('simultaneously', 'O'), ('runs', 'O'), ('Jeff', 'PERSON'), ('through', 'O'), ('with', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('chainsaw', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('killing', 'O'), ('him', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('In', 'O'), ('her', 'O'), ('fortune', 'O'), ('telling', 'O'), ('booth', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('Estrella', 'PERSON'), ('predicts', 'O'), ('death', 'O'), ('for', 'O'), ('Marge', 'PERSON'), (',', 'O'), ('who', 'O'), ('runs', 'O'), ('out', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('terrifed', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('past', 'O'), ('Jerry', 'PERSON'), (',', 'O'), ('Angela', 'PERSON'), (',', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('Harold', 'PERSON'), ('.', 'O')]
[('Estrella', 'PERSON'), ('predicts', 'O'), ('``', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('death', 'O'), ('near', 'O'), ('water', 'O'), ("''", 'O'), ('for', 'O'), ('someone', 'O'), ('close', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('Angela', 'PERSON'), ('.', 'O')]
[('Jerry', 'PERSON'), ('then', 'O'), ('goes', 'O'), ('on', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('violent', 'O'), ('overnight', 'O'), ('rampage', 'O'), ('he', 'O'), ('will', 'O'), ('have', 'O'), ('no', 'O'), ('memory', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('killing', 'O'), ('Marge', 'PERSON'), ('and', 'O'), ('fatally', 'O'), ('wounding', 'O'), ('Bill', 'PERSON'), ('.', 'O')]
[('The', 'O'), ('next', 'O'), ('day', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('Jerry', 'PERSON'), ('attempts', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('strangle', 'O'), ('his', 'O'), ('girlfriend', 'O'), ('Angela', 'PERSON'), ('as', 'O'), ('well', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('The', 'O'), ('zombies', 'O'), ('immediately', 'O'), ('kill', 'O'), ('Estrella', 'PERSON'), (',', 'O'), ('Carmelita', 'PERSON'), (',', 'O'), ('Ortega', 'PERSON'), ('and', 'O'), ('several', 'O'), ('performers', 'O'), ('before', 'O'), ('being', 'O'), ('shot', 'O'), ('by', 'O'), ('police', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
[('Jerry', 'PERSON'), (',', 'O'), ('himself', 'O'), ('partially', 'O'), ('disfigured', 'O'), ('but', 'O'), ('not', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('zombie', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('escapes', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('carnival', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('is', 'O'), ('pursued', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('shoreline', 'O'), (',', 'O'), ('where', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('police', 'O'), ('shoot', 'O'), ('him', 'O'), ('dead', 'O'), ('in', 'O'), ('front', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('Angela', 'PERSON'), ('and', 'O'), ('Harold', 'PERSON'), ('.', 'O')]
[('Estrella', 'PERSON'), ("'s", 'O'), ('prediction', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('``', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('death', 'O'), ('near', 'O'), ('water', 'O'), ("''", 'O'), ('for', 'O'), ('someone', 'O'), ('close', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('Angela', 'PERSON'), ('is', 'O'), ('fulfilled', 'O'), ('.', 'O')]
